[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog ♪
♪ And Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
[LAUGHING]
Yeah!
I found another bike
and more computers!
What do you got?
I keep finding baby shoes!
[FOOSH!]
What the heck, man?!
And they're all lefties!
Sorry
I'm not finding any loot.
Keep it together,
Chubby,
because I think we've
found enough
scrap to finish
building our gauntlet dock --
a dock that is
also a gauntlet!
Aww!
Building this gauntlet
dock is hard, man.
Hard work sucks.
Don't be lazy, Jake.
[SLOSH!]
BOTH:
Huh?
JAKE:
lncoming iceberg!
FINN:
Whoa! That one's huge!
I got dibs!
JAKE:
Ooh, I hope it's not baby shoes!
[GASPS]
It's a guy!
Creepy.
It's a bunch of guys.
JAKE:
You know what they
remind me of?
Well-dressed pickles.
Stand back, Jake.
I'm gonna melt
them out of there,
full charge.
[FOOSH!]
Whoa!
Don't roast them, man!
You got to flambé.
[TRICKLE! TRICKLE!]
Ah! Perfecto!
[SMOOCHES]
Bon appétit!
Hey, can you hear me?
Hello?
[TAP! TAP!]
I don't think
they made it.
Hey, this one's got
some kind of pack --
Aaaaaah!
L...remember...
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
...besinessssssss.
Leggo! Leggo! Leggo!
[CRACK! CRACK! CRACK!]
We... are businessmen.
Ohhhhh.
Well, I'm Finn,
and he's Jake.
What kind of
business do you do?
Been frozen... so long, I --
[ALL GROAN]
...can't remember.
Can't remember!
[BUSINESSMEN CRYING]
Oh.
Looking for help,
your business?
We love work for you.
Nah.
Adventurers don't need any help.
- Yes!
Help us fix that dock!
Dock?
Yeah!
Right over there!
Yes.
This dock...
could be more...
efficient.
FINN:
No! Wait!
[ALL GASP]
Jake, this dock
is our fun pie.
We should be the
ones to bake it.
But they're begging for
it, Finn.
Just look at them!
[ALL TALKING EAGERLY]
Finn, these poor souls are lost
without jobs.
We can't ignore their plight.
Uh...
Go on, guys!
Fix it up!
[ALL CHEERING, SHOUTING]
Well, they do seem
really happy to do it.
Of course, man.
They said they
"love work for you."
[BUSINESSMEN MOAN]
ALL:
We finish.
FINN:
Whoa!
JAKE:
Told you so.
Come on!
Let's try it out!
[BOTH PANTING]
Aaah!
Yeah!
Wh-o-o-o-o-o-oa!
[GRUNTS]
[LAUGHS]
Yeah! Whoo!
[BOTH PANTING]
See?
If we hire them full time,
they'll be back
in business, and
we'll be able to
focus on fun stuff.
Everybody wins!
Maybe you're right.
You hear that, guys?!
Maybe I'm right!
Really? Job?
With... adventurers?
Yeah, mans!
[ALL CHEERING]
[STEAM HISSING]
[SPITS]
[VIDEO GAME BEEPING]
Feels weird doing nothing.
Relax, man.
This is your day off.
WOMAN:
Help! Somebody help!
Trouble, dude!
Get your ax!
I'll get my -- wha?
Adventure pack --
ready for you!
Hey, thanks, man.
[BOTH PANTING]
I have to say, Jake,
my sword is
totally shiny
and stinkin' sharp.
Uh-huh!
Even my shoes
feel different.
Not only are they clean,
I feel
radder, faster,
more adequate.
Cool.
[ALL PANTING]
Help!
Don't cry,
Hot Dog Princess!
Jake and I
will fend off these
battle cubes!
[ALL TALKING INDISTINCTLY]
[FINN AND JAKE GRUNTING]
[GRUNTING GROWS WEAKER]
Man.
I'm getting tired.
Ohh. Me too.
These cubes are...
whew!
...frickin' resilient.
JAKE:
Hey, business-dudes!
ALL:
Huh?
Hold off these cubes so
we can catch our breath?
Jake, they don't know
how to fight.
[BUSINESSMEN SHOUTING]
Water, orange slices.
Help rehydrate.
Arrrghh!
These guys are great, right?
I got to admit...
Oooogggggggh!
They are helping. Oh!
I think I figured out how to
defeat the battle cubes!
That's 'cause you had
time to rest your body and
refresh your brain.
Okay!
We'll take it from here, guys!
Yeah! Good work!
Rawwrrr!
Grab all the cubes
together!
Got 'em!
Aaaah!
[SQUEAK! SQUEAK!]
It worked!
Wake up, Hot Dog Princess.
You're free.
Oh!
Thank you, Finn and Jake!
Especially you, Finn.
[GIGGLES, SMOOCHES]
Ugh!
She smells like
old hot dog water!
[LAUGHS]
Her!
Mwwwwwwwwwah!
[GIGGLES]
I take one for team.
This is awesome!
You get a promotion, fella!
Whooooo!
Take one for team, too.
Yayyyy!
[VIDEO GAME BUZZES]
Oh! Lost again!
My turn.
[VIDEO GAME BEEPING]
[MONITORS BEEPING]
What's that?
Herovision monitor.
Use satellite to tell
us world problems.
Oh, wow.
Anything going on?
Just small things.
You save stress
for blg thing.
Freakin' awesome, man.
What are they doing?
Taking care of business.
[LAUGHS]
[CHOMP! CHOMP!]
[GRUNTING]
Jake, hit me.
[CHOMP!]
[BEEPING CONTINUES]
[SLURPS]
COMPUTER:
Mission complete.
Yeah!
We beat "Adventure Master"!
Holy moly!
♪ We're Adventure ♪
♪ Masters ♪
Yes!
[BOTH PANTING]
BOTH:
Whew!
I never knew being fat
and lazy was so rewarding.
Yeah.
Your gut's so
huge and moldable.
Hey! Hold on a sec.
[LAUGHS]
Man, that tickles.
[AS LCE KING]
I'm the lce King,
and I'll never find a bride,
because I'm such a tool.
[LAUGHS]
All right, let me try.
[GRUNTING]
[AS BUBBLEGUM]
I'm Princess Bubblegum,
and I'm a
dork because
I like science.
I've also got a
really annoying
voice that Finn
thinks is attractive.
[LAUGHS]
That's --
Hey, what'd you say?
Aaaaaah!
Oh, my gosh!
Leave me alone!
All I said was,
"You're ugly,"
which is totally true!
Somebody help me!
Ugh!
Man, I am not
in the mood for
saving
Lumpy Space Princess.
Hey, business-dudes!
ALL:
Hup! Hup! Hup!
What do you guys think?
Mm...
just one monster.
We do. Right.
We'll just save
our strength for
the Blg Adventures, then.
[SIGHS]
Nice call, dude.
Imagine how awesome the
adventure's
going to be when
it's time for us
to go out there.
I'm too tired to
imagine stuff,
but I bet you're right.
BOTH:
To being Great Adventurers.
[GLUG! GLUG! GLUG! GLUG!]
Ehh...
Ungggh...
Eugggggh!
Ooh. Aah!
Oof!
Oh, gosh.
VOICES:
Help us!
Huh?
Jake!
Did you hear that?
Yeah.
Let the businessmen handle it.
VOICES:
Help! Please!
I heard it again.
Businessmen, dude!
He-e-e-e-e-lp!
[GASPS]
[ALL SCREAMING]
[POP!]
Whoo-hoo!
Jake!
We messed up!
The businessmen have gone
bat-crazy, dude!
Man, just let the
businessmen handle it!
The businessmen
are the problem,
you lazy plughole!
Huh?
Guys!
[GRUNTING]
Guys, stop it!
Stop it, guys!
Stop what, boss?
You're jacking up those
fuzzy friends!
But...
We're being heroes --
like you, boss.
We're protecting them --
collecting them
in our care sack
so they cannot be hurt.
[ALL SCREAMING]
It's the most efficient way
to save people.
But you're making
them unhappy!
Irrelevant.
These people are
in our care sack.
Their happiness
is not priority.
I am your boss!
And you guys are all fired!
Fi-red?
[ALL SHOUTING ANGRILY]
[POP! POP! POP! POP! POP!]
[POP!]
[SCREAMING]
[THUD!]
N-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o!
All right, guys,
now I got to
take you down --
Finn-style!
[PANTING]
Aah!
Unh!
I'm kicking your
care sack, dudes!
Finn?
Aw, crud!
[GRUNTS]
[CRE-E-E-E-E-AK!]
I'm coming, buddy!
[POP!] [THUD!]
Oof!
[POP! POP!]
Agh!
I'm so fat, dude,
I don't know
what to do!
[GASPS]
That's it!
Jake! Demoralize them!
What? Why?
Do it, man.
I have a legit plan.
Okay, all right. Hey!
You guys are
horrible at business!
ALL:
Rawwwwwr!
Huh?
They're sucking me up, dude!
Now -- eat that ice
cream some more,
to become fatter,
while also using your
stretchy powers
to grow huge!
Okay!
[MUNCH! MUNCH!]
Rawwwwwwwr!
Aaaaah!
This sucks!
Yeah, dude!
Keep growing!
You're breaking
apart their robot!
ALL:
Wh-o-o-o-o-o-o-oa!
Oh, no!
[BOOM!]
ALL:
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
I'm going to kill you,
not-boss!
Wait, man! Wait!
I want to re-hire you guys!
Re-hire?
Really?!
Yeah, mans.
[BUSINESSMEN CHEERING]
Happy!
[FUZZY FRIENDS CHEERING]
Hip-hip hooray!
[SLOSH!]
So, wait --
what'd you
hire them to do?
I hired them to stuff
themselves in that
iceberg and get out of here.
[SIGHS]
I'm gonna miss them.
And I'm gonna miss this gut.
[SQUISH!]
[CHUCKLES]
I'm gonna miss my gut, too.
[GRUNTS]
Huh?
Awww!
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪