[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very distant
lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
You're totally slow,
dude.
Speed up them gams.
[PANTING] I'm not used to
running on all fours! Aah!
Ready to admit
it's harder than it looks?
I'll never admit
anything to you.
Hey! Where'd you go?
[LAUGHS]
Whoa! Ugh!
Okay, I admit, it's --
it's harder than I thought.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Actually, you did
pretty good.
Hey, check it out.
- Whoa!
Looks like a giant dead
turtle.
I think it's some kind
of city of...
Thieves!
It's the city of thieves!
Be warned, boy!
All who enter the city are
destined to become thieves
themselves.
[LAUGHS]
Even you!
I wouldn't become
a thief, lady!
I'm a pretty good guy.
Yeah, get your glasses
on, grandma.
This kid is pure.
In fact, he's about to help
that little crying kid.
- Oh, whoa!
- Be warned!
Enough, lady!
Hey, little girl, are you okay?
Please, don't steal anything
from me!
Whoa!
We wouldn't do that.
We're heroes.
We wanna turn your frown
all the way around.
Aah!
[CRYING]
- Jake!
- I'll face the other way...
but I'm gonna keep
doing this.
So, what's wrong?
Oh, it was terrible.
I was trying to sell my flowers
out here in the desert
when these two thieves came
and stole my whole basket,
then ran into the city.
- The city?
- Of thieves!
Oh, boy.
Heed my warning, boy!
Enter the city,
and you'll come out a thief!
Never!
I'll get this girl's flowers back.
My name's Penny.
I'll get Penny's flowers back
and come out of that city
as pure as the driven snow.
Let's go, Jake!
Yeah!
We're gonna purify that city!
[THIEVES LAUGHING]
[PANTING]
- Cool!
- Crud.
My ring!
[BOTH GASP]
Stop, thief!
- Rrr!
- Aah!
Stop!
My ruby!
Stop, baby!
Don't steal!
[CRYING]
Don't steal, Mr. Turtle.
Finn, it's hopeless to try
stopping a thief here.
Everyone steals
from each other.
It's ri-doo-doo-diculous!
Penny!
Never say that!
"Ri-doo-doo-diculous"?
No, the whole thing you said --
about hopelessness.
'Cause I'm gonna get your basket
back from whoever took it,
and then I'm going to beat
my purity into them!
And then I'm gonna beat
your purity out of them
and then beat a sandwich
into them.
[GRUNTING]
And then beat them
to the punch!
And then punch them!
- We can beat these thieves
while we search
for Penny's flower basket.
Okay! Yah!
Hey, "Turd-le."
I'm gonna kick your butt!
Also, have you seen this little
girl's flower basket?
You're going down,
Turtle!
Whoa.
L want jets.
Yah!
Come back,
crossbow guy!
Ha ha!
My crossbow!
Hey! My basket!
That's my basket!
Don't worry, Penny.
We'll get it right after I deal
with this guy.
Stealing's wrong, doofus!
[CHUCKLES]
This is fun, Finn!
Whoo!
[LAUGHING]
- Poodaw!
- My bro!
My body!
I'm gonna steal your flower
basket, wizard!
Pancake, pancake, pancake.
Meow!
[LAUGHS STUPIDLY]
- Whoa, brother!
- Yah!
My glasses.
[LAUGHS]
My jammies!
My glasses!
Ow!
- There it goes!
[GIGGLES]
I will smite thee,
goblin thief!
You stole that basket
from me.
No, I didn't.
Hey! Gimme that!
I stole it first!
I'll use my sword on you.
Hey!
You, there!
It's time to step inside
the purification chamber, son.
Hey!
[LINE SQUEAKING]
Huh?
[PANTING]
How are we supposed to get
that basket back
if it keeps being
stolen?! Ugh!
Hey! We can steal a new one
from that guy.
He's got lots of flower
baskets... and boots.
I'd like to steal me one of them
pairs of boots, especially.
No, Jake.
We can't steal.
We have to stay pure.
O-kay.
I have an idea.
My mom used to tell me that
there's a king of thieves
who lives in the center
of the city,
and everything that gets stolen
from little girls
ends up at his tower.
Maybe we'd find my basket
in his treasure chest.
That's a great idea,
Penny.
There's one thing, though.
The tower that he lives in
is surrounded by a magical barrier
which magically
keeps thieves out.
Have you forgotten?
We three ain't thieves.
We're pure!
Right, Jake?
Jake?
Just gotta steal
these boots.
- Jake!
- Huh?
- Hey, go away!
- What are you doing, man?
It's the city!
It's getting to me!
Help me, Finn!
- I'm here for you, buddy.
Thank you, Finn.
Thank you.
Rah!
No!
I won't let you become a thief!
Uh, what are these?
Bells.
That way, I'll hear if you try
to steal again.
Oh! Hmm.
[BELLS JINGLING]
The king of thieves' tower is
right up here.
[BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY]
Whoa!
You ready to pass through,
Penny?
I'm too afraid.
Is it okay if I wait out here?
Sure.
Come on, let's go, Jake!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Coming.
Jake, where'd you get
those boots?
Huh? What?
What boots?
Oh, no!
I stole!
The city --
it took advantage of me!
Ugh!
Jake, you're a thief now.
You won't be able to get in
anymore.
Yes, I can.
Oof!
Oh. Heh!
[SIGHS]
it's up to me now.
Legend says you'll find the loot
in the king of thieves'
chest.
Good luck, Finn.
Oh, yeah, and that high window
is the only entrance.
Hmm.
All right, wish me luck.
- She already did, man.
- Oh, yeah.
Right.
[GRUNTING]
Whoo!
Yeah, Finn!
Ugh!
Great, now I gotta
climb down?
Huh?
[SCREAMING]
Whoa!
The king of thieves.
Uh... sorry to trespass.
I just, uh...
Hello?
The chest!
It's In his chest.
Thanks.
[RAT SQUEAKS]
Aah!
You see, if you have
too much earwax,
you won't be able
to hear anymore.
- I got it, guys!
- The chest!
Gimme that!
- Huh?!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Easy, kid.
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
Wha?! l-ls your basket
under all that gold?
Of course it's not!
I set you up to steal
this chest of gold!
I couldn't get past the barrier
'cause I'm a thief!
But you're just a cute
little girl!
And I'm a thief!
Well, if this isn't yours,
I'm gonna return it right now!
Huh?
Why can't I...
You stole something
in the city.
Now you're a thief!
No.
No-o-o-o!
What have I done?!
What have I become?!
You've become a thief,
stupid.
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
My hands, they're all dirty,
covered in the dust
of a criminal act.
I'm a thief!
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
Huh?
Whoa! Ugh!
Ooh, what did I tell you,
boy?
This city will get to you,
no matter how pure
you think you are!
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
I was right.
Hey!
That's enough from you, hag!
Aah! Hey!
Finn?
Don't touch me!
I'm impure, man!
Unfit to be a hero.
Unfit to be your friend.
Come on, Finn.
Keep it together.
No, Jake.
This is a one-way path
down a jacked-up road,
and I got to walk it...
alone.
I'm not gonna leave you
alone in this city.
You're my buddy.
Besides, I stole these boots.
These super-babe-style boots.
So I'm just as dirty
as you are, Finn.
We got to walk this filthy path
together.
Then we shall embrace
the darkness of this wicked city
and use the methods
of the criminal
to seek vengeance
on Penny.
Cowabunga!
Cowabunga, indeed.
[NEIGHING]
Yah!
[WHINNIES]
PENNY:
Mm. Yes.
Yeah.
Wha?!
Is someone there?
Hmm. Heh.
- Penny.
- Huh?
It's me, Penny --
the hero
whose purity you stole.
And I'm here to enact
my revenge upon you.
Aah!
Hi, Penny.
Finn, please don't
punch my lights out.
I'm just a poor
homeless baby girl!
I trusted you, Penny.
You made me steal.
And you took my purity.
You ruined me!
I'm sorry, Finn!
Let me give you some, uh, gems
or some gold.
Or, uh, have some...
knife in your neck!
- Watch out, Finn!
- Aah!
Oof! Ow! Ugh!
- Thanks, dude.
- Yeah, dude.
You may have soiled my purity,
but I think you can
still come out clean.
Come on, Jake!
[CHUCKLES]
No! No!
[BLUBBERING]
Nice work, dude.
FINN:
She's purified.
I feel... clean,
like all the filth of the city
and wrongdoings are gone.
Thank you, "F" and "J."
I haven't felt like this
since I was young!
You're welcome!
Whoa, dude!
The soap got on us, too.
We're clean!
BOTH:
Yes!
This good deed we did
has purified us once again.
We're virgin islands!
Finn, thank you for this
second chance to live a purer life.
And you know what that
means, Penny.
No more stealing.
- Never again.
Well, I think it's time for us
to get the math out of here.
I'm going to miss you, Finn!
- I'll miss you, too.
- Goodbye.
Whoa, dude.
- Why are you naked?
- Aah!
Penny!
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪