[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very
distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
FINN:
Safety... Patrol!
JAKE:
Safety patrol!
Safety -- oh, were we
not wearing the uniforms?
Come on.
Let's keep looking for hazards.
Look out!
What is it, Dude?
Shushers, man.
Look there.
Just looks like an
ordinary little town, man.
Yeah.
Suspiciously ordinary.
Oh, little house people.
Maybe it is just regular ordinary,
not sinister ordinary.
Oh, no, wait.
Grass Ogre.
[CHUCKLES]
Hey, chicken!
You're traveling
"Eggspress."
[LAUGHS]
It's an obnoxious grass Ogre.
You get my joke, right?
[LAUGHS]
Careful, you oaf!
Those chickens are rentals!
Oh!
We're having so
much fun, huh?
[LAUGHS]
Drop that chicken. Huh?
You're under arrest.
[STOMP!]
[CHICKEN CLUCKING]
Good.
Now get in your tiny cell.
Uh, oh.
Oh, uh, uh...
[LAUGHING]
Hey, Ogre!
Stop hazing these
cute little houses!
Yeah, jerk ball!
My name is Donny, idiot.
Sorry, I was just trying
to get your attention.
What kind of houses
are you supposed to be --
uh, stupid,
uh... a dumb house?
[LAUGHS]
Hey, what's with your jowl?
Ow!
[LAUGHS]
I'm gonna mess with these
housies some more.
Never! Ugh!
So, you want to wrestle, huh?
'Cause I know,
like, this Ninja
move to get out of
this lock instantly.
[GRUNTING]
Okay, now, first, I --
[GRUNTS]
Hey, you're doing it wrong!
Stop cheating!
Whoa.
You're doing it wrong.
What do you mean?
First, you roll your
right shoulder forward.
Ugh, like this?
Yeah, but then I
counter it by doing this.
Hey.
[LAUGHS]
[GRUNTING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Um, you need
to take a break?
No.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
But if you need to, we can stop.
You baby.
Whoa, I zoned out
there for a bit.
Did you win?
Nah, just taking five.
Donny's pretty good.
Yeah, well, you're okay, too.
Thanks, man.
DONNY:
For a complete idiot!
Aww.
- [LAUGHS]
Donald, quit all this
jerky nonsense!
Ugh!
Unless you went to get
gored by a forest Prince!
I was just kidding around.
But then you took it too far.
You guys are the real jerks.
[MUMBLING]
Pshh!
Donny is one
mixed-up dude.
Nah, he's just
rough-and-tumble like me.
But deep down, he's probably
really sensitive like me.
You're a mixed-up dude, too.
- Hey, Donny!
- What?
I was thinking that since
you're a pretty good wrestler,
maybe you'd want to
hang out with a couple of
rascals like me and Jake.
What?
Uh, I don't know.
Messing with these
housies is pretty fun.
You got something better?
You sure this
is a good idea?
If you come to the tree fort,
we got video games and apple juice.
Really?!
I mean...
Fine.
If it keeps you from crying.
Donny's problem is that he's
treated as an outsider, like me.
You are not an outsider.
You wear cute little blue shorts.
L...am complicated.
DONNY:
Uh, this fort isn't so great.
Not as cool as the fort
I'm gonna build.
I call this chair!
Hey, Donny.
You should play
"Bug Battle."
And, hey, can you
put on some pants?
You put on some pants!
I have pants spun from
spider webs by Pixies.
Okay, there's you,
and here come the bugs.
Uh, yeah.
[CHUCKLING]
Huh?
Oh, yeah.
Those guys will get you.
Ugh! This game cheats!
Ohh.
[THUD]
Not cool, dude.
Have more apple juice.
It always makes me
feel better when I -- ugh!
Donny, quit being a jerk!
What? What did I do?
Ugh!
Finn, I don't think
this is gonna work.
I am incapable
of all emotion,
but you are making
me chaffed.
Everybody's getting mad
at me for nothing!
You have to think about
how your actions make
other people feel.
Oh. Hmm.
I don't understand at all.
Ooh, teach him that little
empathy song I taught you.
Okay, yeah.
♪ Empathy, empathy ♪
♪ Put yourself in
the place of me ♪
Your turn.
- Uh...
♪ Empathy, empathy ♪
♪ Put yourself... ♪
Oh!
So it's like when I squeeze
eggs out of chickens,
I should let them squeeze
eggs out of me, too.
Um... kind of right.
Ugh! Ugh!
Someone needs our help!
Jake, you stay here and try to fix
him while I deal with an unknown,
possibly deadly emergency.
Dude, trade me jobs.
[THUD]
DONNY:
Jake, somebody broke your,
um, entire living room!
[GROWLING]
Quick -- act abandoned!
[WHIMPERS]
Hands off the housing market!
[GROWLING]
Whoa! Hey! Ow!
Backpack!
Werewolves --
much worse than ogres.
Whoa!
Stop in the name of the law.
Is there somewhere
I can trap that thing?
Well, we had a zoo,
but he moved back East.
Of course,
there's always the old well.
I'm not old.
Perfect!
[SNORTING]
Ha! Ha!
[WHIMPER ECHOING]
Slam bam in a can.
[GROWLS]
Huh?
Another werewolf?
What's up with this town?
[SCREAMING]
[SCREAMS]
[WHIMPER ECHOING]
[THUD]
Mr. Bank, are you all right?
Oh, it's fine. it's fine.
All my assets are insured.
Pardon, I have to go
spackle my cracks.
Oh.
Why is this town just
getting worse and worse?
[EVIL VOICE]
Yes.
Why, indeed?
Hey, what are you
werewolves up to?
We're not werewolves!
[GROWLS]
[ROARS]
[NORMAL VOICE]
We're Why-wolves.
Uh, Why-wolves?
Creatures possessed
by the spirit of inquiry.
[EVIL VOICE]
And bloodlust!
What?
[NORMAL VOICE]
Please.
Save your questions
until the end of the lecture.
Our ecosystem -- at the bottom level
are the house people.
Given the opportunity, we Why-wolves
would easily wipe them out.
[GROWLING]
However...
[LAUGHS]
...Donny's presence is
a natural deterrent.
His jerkiness is so powerful that it
produces a pungent gas, obnoxygen.
To Why-wolves,
it is a deadly poison.
[WHIMPERING]
But since you've removed
the jerk Donny...
[SCREAMING]
...We will devour the houses,
and our population will rapidly
swell until we are, in turn,
devoured by
the cosmic owl.
Hoo!
Such is the course of nature.
But it'll be a pretty sweet
ride up until that point.
[EVIL VOICE] Tonight we feast
on the blood of the innocent!
[SNARLS]
[HOWLING]
[LAUGH EVILLY]
Oh, no!
I have to get Donny back!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Donny, you have to go right now
and stop the Why-wolves from --
Aah, Master Finn has returned.
What's it going?
Thanks to you,
I shall never be jerky again.
Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
No, this is all wrong!
We need Jerk Donny to make the
obnoxygen and -- and --
Steady on, Finn.
Perhaps you're dehydrated.
It's as Jake taught me.
♪ Eight ounces, eight glasses,
eight days a week ♪
I'll fetch you some tap water.
Are you wearing jeans now?
Surely.
♪ Got to get pants ♪
♪ Go get your pants ♪
♪ Button fly! ♪
I wrote that one myself.
Perdóname.
But, but, but...
But, but, but,
yeah, Donny!
You're looking good
in those jeans.
What did you do?!
Miraculous, isn't it?
I just kept teaching him my musical
rules, and now he's perfect.
No! We messed up, Jake!
The house people are doomed if Donny
doesn't go back to being town jerk!
[CLEARS THROAT]
I've no intention of
being a jerk again.
Hmm.
But the housies will
be wiped out if you don't.
It sounds tragic,
but I'm turning over a new leaf.
Donny, you got to go!
Finn, no means no.
I'm sure you'll
respect my wishes.
No! Stop! No!
[WHY-WOLVES SNARLING,
HOUSIES SCREAMING]
Now, go be a jerk to
those Why-wolves.
No.
[SNARLING, SCREAMING CONTINUE]
I'll use my musical messages
to stop them.
Let's see.
I've got one on the ethics of laundry,
"Crosswalkery."
Ooh, here's a good one.
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
Man, the town is getting creamed!
By not being a jerk,
you're being a real jerk, Donny.
♪ Comb your hair right ♪
♪ It's a good time ♪
♪ Sticky, sticky pomade ♪
♪ Short back and sides ♪
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
Why isn't anyone paying
attention to my words?
He sure is sensitive
about his songs.
[GASPS]
It's 'cause they think
your songs are dumb!
Wha?
What are you saying?
If we don't encourage his talent,
he might revert back
to jerk Don--
oh, oh!
Hey, Donny, everyone says
your songs are super balls.
They all think
you're a real jerk!
But --
but I've changed!
Why would they say that?
♪ Empathy, empathy ♪
♪ Put your mind inside -- ♪
[LAUGHTER]
You are so pathetic...
so comical.
[LAUGHS]
[GROWLING]
Think I'm a jerk, do they?
I'm feeling... obnoxious!
[ROARS]
You wolves are cool!
Just kidding!
[LAUGHS]
Obnoxygen cloud!
Egress!
[WHY-WOLVES WHIMPERING]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
ALL:
The town is saved! Yay!
Get off of me, nerds!
You did it, Donny.
You're a full-blown jerk again.
What?!
You're the jerk!
Housies, ready to
hear my new song?
It's about how Finn will betray
you just to save lives.
I'm sorry, Donny.
I'll never forgive you, Finn!
[ROARING]
Come on.
We can go stare
wistfully at the lake.
I'd --
I'd like that very much.
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
Hey! I love being a jerk!
Thanks, Finn.
Finn?
Finn, you loser.
[SNIFFLES]
I'll never...
forget you.
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪