[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very
distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
PRINCESS BUBBLEGUM:
All right, guys,
hammer all these safety signs
around this dungeon hole.
I've got to jet off on my swan
to take care of some royal junk.
You got it, Princess.
Whatever you want,
mama.
Bubblegum, away!
[GRUNTING]
Ow. Ow. Ow.
There.
That's the last sign, Jake.
Now no one will ever go down
this hole ever.
Probably a lot of dangerous,
awesome stuff down this hole.
I better go
take a look.
[GRUNTING]
Don't, dude.
For you see...
that's the secret entrance
to the dungeon
of the crystal eye.
Whoa.
Legend has it
that the eye rests
in the deepest chamber
of this accursed dungeon.
Man, we shouldn't even be
talking about it...
'cause it's lunchtime.
[TING!]
[ELEPHANT TRUMPETS]
The crystal eye.
I want to meet this dungeon.
Maybe after lunch.
Eh, I'll skip lunch.
Just catch up to me
when you finish.
[SCOFFS] Yeah, right. - What?
Without the aid
of my magnificent powers...
[GRUNTS]
Huh? Huh?
You'd get killed down there.
Hey, I can do things
without you!
You want to bet I can't?
Nope.
Come get your sandwich.
Listen to Jake, Finn.
He only wants what's best for --
[MUFFLED]
Aah! Help me!
Aah!
Come put her out of her misery,
dude!
We are betting!
I bet that I'll get that crystal eye
and be back within
11 minutes!
Ready set go!
[SIGHS]
I better go after him.
No, Jake.
Stay here... With me.
[DEEPLY]
Oh, my.
Dungeons!
Chambers!
Whoa!
Evil creatures!
[LAUGHING]
Treasure chests!
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
[LAUGHING]
Whoo!
[CREATURE VOMITING]
Doorways!
Traps!
Yah!
I'm in my eleme-e-e-e-e-e-nt!
[PURRING]
Huh?
Meow?
Oh!
Mroooooow...
Oh?
[PURRING]
Whoa!
Somebody come pick up
your freaky cat!
Greetings...
Frank the human boy.
How did you almost know
my name?!
I have approximate knowledge
of many things.
For instance, I know that I am
possibly going to slay you
and munch
on your eyeballs.
Heh. Yeah, right.
That sounds like idiot talk.
You're trespassing
on my dungeon, manling.
And I am the thing...
you should be afraid of.
You can't hurt me!
I'm a radical boy on a mission
for the crystal eye!
I'm going to unzip your skin
and wear you like a little coat.
Unzip this!
[ARMPIT SQUEAKS]
Ha!
[ROARS]
Bleep! Oof!
[GRUNTING]
Yeow!
Now you die!
[ROARS]
- Aah!
- Wait a second.
[SNIFFS]
Is that dog smell?!
You -- you have a dog
with you?
I'm out of here!
Yeah, right!
Good excuse!
Slaps.
That cat was kicking my buns.
And it might
have finished my buns
if it weren't for Jake's
stank.
Dang it, Jake!
I'll get that crystal eye
on my own!
With my own odors.
Pressing on!
Let's see.
No to skeletal-remains door.
[DEEP BREATHING]
Whoa!
No to giant
monster mouth door.
Oh!
Giant key door it is!
If Jake was here,
he could stretch his hand
into a key and open it.
[GRUNTS]
Yeah! Key hand!
[GRUNTING]
Ouch.
Hey. What the jug is that?
Oh, sweet! The key!
♪ Oh, key
we're meant to be ♪
♪ L want to have
your baby ♪
♪ Oh, key,
you're so good to me ♪
Ugh!
Jelly cube?!
[GRUNTS]
Come on!
Give it to me!
Don't flaunt it if you're not
gonna give it up!
[GRUNTING]
[HIGH-PITCHED SCREECH]
Unh!
[SIGHS]
I'll never get that crystal eye!
No.
No, I just got to stay pumped.
Pump it up!
Whoo! Whoo!
Shake it, shake it!
Whoa! Oof!
Steady, Finn.
This place is probably more
creeped out of you
than you are of it.
Hup!
MAN:
Halt!
Come no further, adventurer!
For you see, none can defeat...
the bucket knight!
Okay.
Then I won't fight you.
No! You must
challenge me to --
Hey, cutie, do you know how
to get the crystal eye from here?
Yes, it's through that door
over there, but --
- Thanks!
- Hey!
[LAUGHING]
You can't pass through that
door without battling me!
Yes, I can!
Because I'm huge
compared to you!
Just add water and...
exponential growth!
Aw, buckets.
Now activate
thine own powers,
and we shall engage
in thrilling single combat!
Heh, thing is...
I don't really have any powers.
I see.
Aaaaaaaah!
Dang it!
Jake wouldn't be running!
He'd grow all big.
And sock you
right in the nose hole!
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
Whoa! Aah!
Aw, nutzoids!
Haaah!
[GROANING]
Come on!
All aboard the knuckle train
to fist planet!
Oof! Unh!
[GROANS]
L rode the knuckle train?
But...
I'm in my element.
[PANTING]
[GASPS]
Yaaaaaah!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Unh!
That sucked.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
All right, Finn.
You're in a heavy pickle here.
You don't have Jake,
but you can
still handle this!
Meow?
You can still get that
crystal eye!
[HUMMING]
Hey...
my dinner is back.
And your dog isn't with you.
That's what you said, right?
Jack the dog is not
"accompanying" you?
You mean Jake?
Jake, jack, whatever.
He's not here,
which means
I'm going to rip your heart out.
Crud, crud,
crud, crud, crud!
You can't hide from me, Jim!
I know almost everything,
remember?!
I know exactly where
you might be, Jim.
I'm about to pounce on you.
One...
two...
three!
Aw, man!
Thought you'd be
behind this rock.
Hmm.
[SNIFFS]
All right, I know
where you are now,
and I'm about to pounce
again!
1 ...2...3!
[THUDS]
Aw, man!
Well, there's only a few more
places to look.
Oh, Jake...
I'm such a fool!
A silly, silly fool!
Shh.
Who the heck --
Hey...
it's okay.
Shh.
I'm your guardian angel, Finn.
I'm here to save you.
R-Really?
Mm-hmm.
Come here.
Let the angel pick you up.
Oh. Okay.
[LAUGHING]
This is radical!
Are you comfortable?
Would you like some snacks?
I'm fine, thank you.
Here. Let me clean you up
and mend your clothes.
[LAUGHING]
I'm taking you to the chamber
of the crystal eye...
Aw, yeah!
...where I'm going to cook you
and eat your flesh.
Wow...
Wait. What?!
Trust in your...
guardian angel!
Put me down, lady!
As you wish.
Waaah! Unh!
Aw, man.
Everyone wants
to eat me up.
It's probably
'cause I'm so sweet.
Now, for little-kid soup.
The secret is a low flame
over a long period.
That's Jake's secret,
too.
Sure hope he saves me.
I will save thee, Finn.
Lady, you are sick!
- Oh, Jake.
- What?
- Jake!
- Finn!
What are you doing
here?
Heh, heh, I was looking
for you, knucklehead.
I was so worried that,
right after lunch,
I plunged into
the dungeon after you.
Strangest thing, though.
I kept running into obstacles.
Choose your dueling weapon!
Eh... Um...
uh, I choose...
Sandwich!
[SNORTING]
The challenges were
impossible for me.
But you would have blown
right through them.
I kept asking myself,
"what would Finn do?"
Just... frustrating.
You know what I mean.
Yeah, I think I do.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Now let's figure out a way out
of this cage!
Got it covered...
with key hand!
I don't see any keyholes
in this cage, though.
Not a problem, man.
Lock hand!
I'll get us out...
with carrot hand!
Heh heh.
[XYLOPHONE PLAYING]
[WHISTLE!]
Aah!
Come on, man.
We still got
a couple minutes left
to steal that crystal eye
and win your bet!
Wait.
You'd help me win a bet
that I made
about how I could accomplish something
without you?
Just hop on my powdered
doughnut, boy!
Cling!
[LAUGHS]
There it is -- the crystal eye!
Let's give this
the good old friendship lift!
[BOTH GRUNT]
Whoa.
Friendship, g-o-o-o!
Hyah!
At least if I die,
I'll die with
my best friend!
Me too!
Get on my swan!
- Ooh!
- Okay!
[BOTH CHEERING]
I hope you learned
a lesson from all this!
Uh, we learned that two heads are better
than one head?
Working together is better
than not working together?
Whatever.
Grr.
It looks like that's
not the answer she wanted.
Uh...
I learned that
you are a very, uh,
intelligent Princess?
You're darn right I am.
Yeah! All right!
Princess Bubblegum,
awa-a-a-a-a-a-y!
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪