[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
JAKE: And as it waded through
the carnage it had wrought,
the vampire smashed their skulls
just for the fun of it!
No way!
Yes way! it did!
And, also, the vampire
hunched over its victims
and breathed
their vaporized blood mist!
[WARBLING]
Ah, geez!
Jake, is this stuff
you're saying true,
or are you just
trying to mess me up?
You have to be honest.
Oh, it's true, man.
I heard it
through a reliable source.
Reliable? Rats.
Yeah, some say
it haunted this very tree!
- This tree?!
- Good night!
- Jake!
- [WARBLES]
You're full of it, Jake!
JAKE:
[WARBLING OMINOUSLY]
[CREAKING]
[GRUNTS]
[CROAKING]
[GASPS]
[WARBLING]
No worms on the bed!
[WARBLING STOPS]
[SIGHS]
[TAPPING]
Huh?
[THUNDER CRASHES]
[SCREAMS]
Jake! Jake!
I saw someone
outside the window!
It must be the vampire,
and I think we're unprepared, so I --
Relax, buddy.
I made that story up.
I was just trying to scare you.
But you said you heard it
from reliable source.
[CHUCKLES]
I made that up, too.
I was trying to scare you,
and it worked!
[LAUGHS]
Whoa!
[SCREAMS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
No one's outside.
Whew!
It was just the wind,
scaredy-cat.
I wasn't scared.
I was slnglng.
I was singing my scream song.
♪ Aah, aah, aah! ♪
You're a total wuss, man.
[BOTH GASP]
[CHUCKLES]
- [GASPS]
- [HISSES]
[BOTH SCREAM]
Hey, guys. What's up?
I'm Marceline the Vampire Queen.
Are you gonna smash my skull
and breathe my blood mist?!
Don't suck our blood!
[LAUGHS]
Calm down, weenies.
I'm not gonna do that.
So...
You don't suck blood?
Sometimes I do, but it's not
the blood that I like.
It's the color.
I eat shades of red.
Golly!
[SLURPS]
[SIGHS]
[LAUGHS]
Mmm!
[YAWNS, SIGHS]
Wow, I'm exhausted.
I've been traveling all over
the Land of Ooo,
and I've seen some stuff
that would really make you say,
"like what?"
[MUFFLED]
Like what?
I found a School of Goldfish
Beasts.
Yah! Yee-haw!
And I fooled around
in the Fire Kingdom.
[LAUGHING]
Ooh!
Oh, and check these out.
FINN:
Nuts?
Oh, these aren't just
ordlnary nuts.
[GRUNTS]
[ALL WARBLING]
[SCREECHES]
[WARBLING CONTINUES]
[LAUGHS]
You're wonderful.
Yeah, uh, thank you
for not sucking our blood.
You guys seem cool, too.
[YAWNS]
But as you can imagine,
I'm really tired,
so you two should probably
get going.
What?
[SIGHS]
Look.
"M" for "Marceline."
Oh, man.
I carved it in this tree
years ago --
long before you two
rascals started squatting here.
But seriously, guys, thanks for
keeping the place warm for me.
Like, really great. Thanks.
Huh?
Good night!
Come on, Finn,
let's get out of here!
She can't kick us out
of our house!
No, Finn, wait!
Get down here, lady,
and fight me!
She's a vampire, dude!
[LAUGHS]
What?!
[SLURPS]
[SIGHS]
[GRUNTING]
[LAUGHS]
I'm gonna kill her!
Dude, if half the stories I've heard
and/or made up are true,
vamplres
wlll kill you.
There's no question.
[HISSES]
[LAUGHS]
But what about our home?
A vampire took it!
Ah, we should go house hunting --
bag us a new house.
But I like our home.
Finn, house
hunting is wild!
You got to try it!
Really?
Yeah, man.
It is so nuts!
You always
know what to say.
Blah, blee, bloo, blah,
blah, bloobity, blah, bloop!
FINN:
Okay, I'm convinced.
Let's roll!
JAKE: Sweet, things are gonna
start going our way.
JAKE: Hey, look. See?
What did I tell you?
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
♪ So, Finn and Jake ♪
♪ Set out to find a new home ♪
♪ It's gonna be tough ♪
♪ A kid and a dog on their own ♪
♪ There's a little house ♪
♪ Aww, Finn's sticking
his foot in ♪
♪ That's a bad idea, dude,
'cause now that bird thinks
you're a jerk, Finn ♪
♪ Now they're chilling
on the side of a hill
and thinking living in a cloud
would be totally thrilling ♪
♪ Unless they find
something inside,
like a mean cloud man
and his beautiful cloud bride ♪
♪ A beehive -- oh, no ♪
♪ Don't put your foot
in there, guy ♪
♪ Y'all tried that before,
and you know it didn't
turn out right ♪
♪ Big shell -- go inside ♪
♪ Look around,
it seems all right ♪
♪ A frog jumps out
and barfs a tiger,
throwing down a potion
for food and fire ♪
♪ You know
you should have stayed ♪
♪ And fought
that sexy vampire lady ♪
♪ But Jake was feeling
terrified ♪
♪ He was super scared
of her vampire bite ♪
♪ Which is understandable ♪
♪ 'Cause vampires are
really powerful ♪
♪ They're unreasonable and burnt
out on dealing with mortals ♪
♪ Oh, Marceline ♪
♪ Why are you so mean? ♪
♪ I'm not mean,
I'm 1,000 years old ♪
♪ And I just lost track
of my moral code ♪
♪ Oh, Marceline ♪
♪ Can't you see these guys
are in pain? ♪
♪ No, I can't ♪
♪ I'm invested in this very cute
video game ♪
♪ So, there go our boys ♪
♪ Walking on the icy ground ♪
♪ Heading towards
their destiny ♪
♪ I'm sure they'll figure
something out ♪
This is weak!
I don't even llke
any of these places.
I want to go home.
Finn, let me tell you
a little something
about what
"home" really means.
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Home isn't a place ♪
♪ Let me give you a clue ♪
♪ Home is anywhere
where people care about you ♪
I don't want to hear
a lecture, dude.
I just want to go home.
♪ But home is where
your heart is, Finn ♪
♪ And where is your
heart, Finn? ♪
♪ Well, it's right
there inside you ♪
♪ Well, I'm sitting
right here beside you ♪
With your lucky stars
to guide you from above.
[FIDDLE PLAYING]
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Yeah, I guess
I'd rather be out here,
wrapped in your ear,
than be in some
awesome house all by my...
souse.
JAKE: I'd rather be
dancing with some babes.
FINN:
Shut up, dude!
JAKE: Gross. This
place looks gross.
And abandoned.
[ECHOING] And abandoned. And abandoned.
[BOTH SCREAM]
[GASPS]
Whoa, bro!
Want to just live in here?
Yes.
♪ So, they cleaned the cave
and built a house
inside the cave ♪
[SIGHS]
So, what do
you think, man?
We did pretty good for
ourselves.
Yeah, we did.
So, uh, what should we do first
in our new digs?
Let's trash it
and throw a party!
[MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[SIGHS]
This is it.
Feeling good.
Feeling -- I'm feeling
like we did it.
I'm feeling, like,
completely satisfied.
Nothing else can go wrong,
you know, Jake?
- Yeah, man.
- Oh, yeah. I know, too.
Hey, Finn.
- [GASPS]
She's back!
Wow, pretty awesome
party you got here.
What do you want,
Marceline?
Oh, I just want to show
you something.
This cave belongs to me!
What?!
Thanks for fixing
the place up for me.
You -- you can't take
our home twice!
♪ Yes,
I ca-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-n ♪
Aah!
It's vampire-fighting time!
Finn, no!
Vampires will klll you,
remember?
But she's taking
our home again!
We're home as long
as we're together!
Blah, blah, blee, blah,
bloop, remember?
Oh, yeah.
Okay, Marceline,
I'm gonna let you keep this cave,
but only because
Jake is my home.
And he's way better than all
your homes combined!
You know, you're right.
I guess I'll take him, too!
What?!
I'll bite him a little...
Aah!
...maybe turn him into a zombie.
No!
- Let go of Jake!
- Make me.
[GRUNTS]
You okay, pal?
[HISSES]
No one... makes me...
let go of Jake!
I'm not scared of you!
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
You're pathetic, little boy.
[GRUNTS]
You're pathetic!
[HISSES]
Get ready for
an uppercut, you dog!
Make me.
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
Blah, blah!
Blah!
L...
got to help my buddy!
Your blood is mine!
[WARBLING LOUDLY]
[GRUNTING]
- [GASPS]
- Uh-oh.
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
[SCREAMS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Ow!
That... actually hurt, Finn.
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
[SHRIEKS]
[LAUGHS]
Mwah!
W-Why you didn't just kill me?
'Cause that was fun!
Whew, I haven't fought
like that in years.
Thanks, Finn.
Finn.
A-Aren't you dead?
Nah, before she bit me,
I used my powers
to shrink all my guts and blood
over to my thumb, see?
[CLEARS THROAT]
You two are pretty hard core.
I can appreciate that.
So... so does that mean
we can have our old house back?
Yeah, keep it...
as a gift from me!
Blah!
[BOTH SCREAMING]
[LAUGHS]
BOTH:
Yeah! Huh?
[ALL CROAKING]
[ALL WARBLING]
Did you guys
get on the bed?
I told you,
you're not allowed!
MAN:
Oh, hey, guys.
BOTH:
Huh?
Come here, friends. Hug me.
[WARBLING]
Oh, yeah. Hug me.
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪