[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very
distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Walking, walking,
walking -- hambone break!
Whoo-hoo!
Hey, hey, get away from me.
[LAUGHING]
Quit it!
[LAUGHS]
Food for a beggar?
[COUGHS]
Food for a poor old man?
Geez Louise, guy.
So, you got any, kid?
Food?
I got this little
piece of sugar.
[THINKING]
Nuts.
I'm frickin' all about sugar.
But I'm even more all
about feeding hobos!
JAKE:
Wait, Finn.
Maybe helping this starving
homeless guy is the
wrong thing to do.
Why?
I don't know.
L-I said "Maybe."
A hero always helps
someone in need.
And besides, he's probably
secretly an elf who will reward
us for being nice.
Here you go, buddy.
Whoa!
[CHEWING]
You know, believe it or not,
I'm not really a beggar.
I'm actually a...
♪ Magic Man ♪
Whoa! Ah, yeah!
He's -- he's magic!
I didn't --
I didn't expect this.
[WHISTLING]
[BIRD CHIRPING]
Magic!
Away!
[FLAPPING, SQUISHING]
Think happy thoughts --
Little, cute bees, little babies,
tiny, tiny bunnies.
What is wrong with you,
Magic Man?!
You gave me that candy.
Now I'll do you a favor in return --
a magic favor!
♪ A mystical, magical favor ♪
Whoa! Wha-- ugh!
[SCREAMS]
Whoa, dude!
♪ For you ♪
Why'd you do that?!
Because this day, a magical
life lesson comes to you.
No, change me back!
Not until you appreciate
what a jerk I am.
Wazoo!
What a nutty guy.
What the heck, man?!
What kind of deal is that?!
I help somebody out,
and they make me a stinky foot?!
[SNIFFS]
You smell pretty good.
Get off of me, man!
I can't be a hero if I'm a big,
good-smelling foot!
Maybe you're looking at
this magic gift all wrong.
Now that you're a huge foot,
you can kick evil's butt, like,
way more times as hard.
You're 100% kick, man!
Why are you being so
level-headed about this?
Don't be a siss, Finn.
Here, come on, kick my butt.
You're the siss, siss!
Hah! Agh!
Ouch! Ooh, ouch!
See, man?
Let's give your
foot body a shot.
No, dude!
I want to go find that
Magic Man and get my body back!
Shh! Shh! Shh! Shh!
Just be a foot for a llttle bit.
[AS FINN]
Okay, I will.
[AS HIMSELF]
Awesome, dude.
You'll never regret this.
[LAUGHS]
Okay, when the next monster comes
along, he'll step on that
trigger over there, sending your
giant foot body into the
monster's crotch!
This sucks, dude.
Shh!
[ROARING]
We're evil!
[ROARS]
[BOTH SHOUT]
Our crotch --
our evil crotch!
[LAUGHS]
What'd I tell you?
You're a great hero!
Let's go set up some more crotch
catapults so we can laugh
and be heroes.
No, Jake.
Let's find that Magic Man.
Finn, being an enormous
crotch-kicking foot is a gift.
Don't scorn a gift.
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
Town on fire!
This looks like a job for foot
Finn stomping ability!
But I-l can't even bend
these big, fat toes, man.
You can do it, Finn.
What'd I teach you, dude?
Not to scorn the
kicking of people in the crotch?
You got it!
Now I'm gonna go rescue all the
babies in town --
only the babies.
Get your hero on, dude!
Aaaah!
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
Unh!
Okay, you can do this, Finn.
Start small, man.
I'm taking you down!
[GRUNTING]
It's hot!
Oh, man, I'm smoking hot!
Please, help me out!
I can't move!
It's another one of those freaks!
He probably started this fire!
No, I didn't start any --
Throw him under the
bridge with the others!
ALL:
Get rid of the freak!
[CHANTING]
Freak! Freak!
Stay out of our town, freak!
Unh!
[SIGHS]
[SNIFFLES]
I'm not a freak. I'm a hero.
Finn!
Jake, how'd you find me?
Oh, I can sense when
you're about to cry.
It's like a mother/daughter thing.
I'm not gonna cry, man!
I just feel like crying.
We have to find that magic guy
and get my body back now!
What we have to do is find out
what reeks under this bridge.
[SNIFFS]
- Jake!
Ew, it's blocking out
your good foot smell.
Get back here!
Ugh, it -- it smells
like vomit on fire.
It's like fancy cheese
in an old guy's mouth.
Welcome, travelers.
Aah!
I am Gork, leader of Freak City.
Ah, I can see one of you has
felt the Magic Man's touch.
Yeah.
You know that guy?
I will tell you all that I know.
[VOMITS]
We are the accursed ones,
all once normal guys and gals who
crossed paths with the Magic Man.
That's Zap, The Arm.
[MUMBLES]
Trudy, The Waist.
[COUGHS]
That's Wee Wee and Gorflax.
They were turned into tonsils.
And that's Kim.
[CHUCKLES]
[SMOOCHING]
But, please,
make yourselves at home.
Would you like
something to drink?
Do you have any
orange juice?
No.
Well, uh, I don't know.
Maybe. Uh, I don't think so.
I'll go check.
Yo, finn, this place is
really bumming me out.
Let's get out of here.
What?! No, dude.
These guys might be my only
hope of finding the Magic Man.
Hey, we actually do
have orange juice.
Thanks for being cool and all,
but what do you know
about this Magic Man?
How do we catch him?
Oh, he can't be caught.
He's got maglc.
And we're worthless freaks.
We can't ever beat him.
So we've gathered here
to wallow in our self-pity.
But don't y'all
even want to try?
Eh, no.
Why not?
You're all totally
miserable here.
Eh, it's a living.
No, it's not, Zap!
It's not a living!
It's dookie diapers!
I don't want to be a foot!
Well, get used to it.
We did.
Yeah, Finn, maybe there's another
lesson to be learned here --
to accept what fate has given you
and stay a miserable foot.
Gork, can we live here in this
pile of trash and rats forever?
Yeah, man. Do it up.
Awesome.
[RATS SQUEAKING]
Here we go.
Jake,
stop screwing around.
You're gonna make me
give into depression.
Eh, what are you
gonna do about it?
Probably nothing, right?
If you're depressed,
you'll do nothing.
L...
Maybe I will do nothing.
Maybe I'll just lay down here.
[GRUNTS]
[SIGHS]
Lay down -- unh --
and rot like the rest of you.
Yeah!
[CHANTING]
Stay a foot!
Stay a foot! Stay a foot!
♪ Is this really my life? ♪
♪ Is this how my story ends? ♪
♪ Being in this body seems
like a battle that I cannot win ♪
♪ Maybe I should lay my
head down slow ♪
♪ And sleep until
it's all over ♪
♪ Is this the end ♪
♪ Of the hero boy named Finn? ♪
♪ Heck no! ♪
♪ Darn heck no! ♪
♪ This isn't how I go ♪
♪ I'm gonna kill it ♪
♪ I'm gonna kick life's butt ♪
♪ And win it ♪
♪ To win it ♪
♪ I'm gonna take life's name ♪
[SPITS]
♪ And spit on it ♪
♪ And kick it ♪
♪ Life can just go eat it ♪
♪ 'Cause this is a man's game ♪
Get up, Gork!
Huh? Why?
♪ I'm not gonna let you lie here ♪
♪ And waste away ♪
♪ You better get up, Gork,
or I'll kick you up ♪
♪ Today's the day ♪
Whoa, okay, man.
Just be cool.
♪ And I'm not gonna be cool ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm pipin' hot ♪
Ow!
♪ Get up, Trudy ♪
♪ Get up, Kim ♪
♪ I'm not gonna let you rot ♪
[RATS SQUEAKING]
Hey, Finn.
♪ Jake ♪
♪ Stop telling me to enjoy ♪
♪ Being a foot ♪
♪ And get out of that trash ♪
[CHUCKLES]
I can't take you seriously
when you're singing, man.
♪ Get up ♪
- Aah!
♪ All of you make me sick ♪
♪ I'll fix you with my kicks ♪
♪ Gonna reconstruct
y'all's self-worth ♪
♪ Brick by emotional brick ♪
[ALL GRUNTING]
[GRUNTING]
Wait, Finn.
Hey, stop it, man!
We don't like
touching each other.
Huh?
Please, man.
Wait a second.
Kim, get underneath Trudy.
No, man. Please.
I frickin' hate Trudy.
Kim, I will destroy you!
Okay, okay!
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah, do it, Kim.
[STAMMERS]
Yes!
Now for me.
[GRUNTS]
Look at us!
Whoa!
We're like a big, normal guy.
Thank you so much.
We're perfect together.
Oh, Finn, thank you.
Word!
Now let's go wreck
up that Magic Man!
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
Let me get in on this.
I'll form the pants.
MAGIC MAN:
Food. Food for a beggar.
[GASPS]
Y'all got any food?
We've got a little
orange juice left over from --
Wait a second.
That's right.
It is I, the Magic Man!
Zap!
[ALL SHOUT]
Come on, apple grease!
What are you gonna do? Ohh!
We're not afraid!
Are you sure about that?
You're darn right we are!
[VOMITS]
Whoop!
Give us our bodies back!
[SHOUTS]
Why should I?
You still act like a hero only so
you can get what you want.
Oh.
You were trying to teach us to
be kind without expecting
anything in return.
I should've given
you that sugar
cube without even thinking
about a reward.
Wrong!
Whoa! Whoa!
- Ah, geez!
- Finn!
You've gifted us nothing
but heartache, Magic Man!
What's the life lesson in that?!
[LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
Yes, my children,
you are so close to the answer.
Answer this!
Get his eyes!
Cut him in the eyes!
I wish I'd never been nice to you
'cause you're just a big jerk!
Oh, yes, that's it!
You've finally
learned your lesson.
And now I'm off to spread my
teachings to more sissy do-gooders.
You're welcome!
Man, I frickin' hate that guy.
But at least now we can all
go back to our regular lives.
Well, actually...
We like being like this.
Yeah, we're strong together.
ALL:
Bye, Finn! Thank you!
Oh, okay. Bye, guys.
See you later.
Wait, so, what was the
lesson we just learned?
Maybe it was,
don't give your sugar to jerks.
Speaking of jerks,
what the blubins, man?!
Why wouldn't you help
me turn back into a boy?!
Well, because I kind of
always wanted [MUMBLES]
What?
I said, "I kind of always
wanted to be a foot myself."
You could be a
foot right now.
I saw you change into
a foot twice yesterday.
It's complicated, man.
You'll understand
when you're older.
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪