[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go
to very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
SQUID: You guys sure you want
another round of squid ink?
[GIGGLES]
BOTH:
Ahh!
[ALL SHOUTING, GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
- Ha ha!
[STRAINS]
You're not too bad
for a human boy.
Not too bad?
I'm better than that.
Huh?
[SOBBING]
Rrrr-yah!
Jake,
do you hear that?
What'd you say?
Wha! Whoa!
I think someone's
crying.
- Rah! Ha ha!
- Stop! This is serious!
I gotta go find out where that
crying is coming from.
Get back here, you chicken!
[JEERING]
What did you call me?
You can't just walk away
from a roughhouse!
Hey! Listen up,
you cold-hearted marauders.
Somebody's out there
crying for help,
and I'm not gonna
ignore that.
Oh, here it comes.
Lay it down, Finn!
A long time ago,
when I was a baby,
I went boom-boom
on a leaf.
Boom! Boom!
Then I fell backwards and sat In
my own boom-boom.
I crled for a day...
[SOBBING]
...but no one came to help me.
That day, I vowed to help
anyone In need,
no matter how small
thelr problem.
And that's why I need to go.
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
That's what I'm talking
about.
- Yeah!
- Way to go, Finn.
He still cries
when he poops.
Thanks for being cool, guys.
Wait up, Finn!
[SOBBING]
It's coming from
up there.
Someone must be caught
in that avalanche.
Let's get it on.
[SOBBING CONTINUES]
So... who's crying?
I am.
Whoa!
Aww. What's wrong, fella?
You crying boulders?
Yes.
I am sad, having been
forced to watch
roughhousing men
for centuries.
Oh! I see.
You're feeling left out, and you
want to roughhouse, too!
Well, I'll take you on,
tough guy.
Come on,
back me up, Jake.
Yeah, do it, Finn!
Hit him with a boulder.
And then hit him
with another rock.
Please!
No roughhousing.
It m-makes me...
so... sad!
What? Why?
Because they're so rough
on each other.
But a smooth,
well-controlled roughhouse
bolsters your guts
and, uh...
rejuvenates the muscle.
No!
It's raunchy and maddening.
All those men and their
disgusting fantastic bodies.
Whoa.
This guy's got problems.
[GASPS]
[SOBBING]
Look, Mommy.
Honey, don't look.
That kid's got problems.
[SOBBING CONTINUES]
I'll help you, Mountain.
- Whoa! What?!
I'll stop those
roughhousers from being rough.
Really?
You'd do that for me?
Yes, sir.
My name's Finn...
and I'm gonna
help you out.
But, Finn, we're not gonna
shut down the roughhouse
for real, are we?
No way, but there's got
to be some kind of solution.
I'll figure this out,
Mountain Man, yep.
[ALL SHOUTING, GRUNTING]
Hey, you guys.
- Ah, Finn.
Ready to get destroyed?!
N-No.
[CHUCKLES]
Uh, wait.
Um...
actually, can you guys
s-stop being so rough?
ALL:
What?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you talking about, Finn?
Could you... just tone down
the roughhousing a-a little?
- What?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, it's all right, fellas.
Finn, I'm sure this "tone down
the roughhousing" thing
has something to do
with your boom-boom,
and I can respect that.
But how can we possibly make
roughhousing less rough?!
[MOUSE SQUEAKS, DUCK QUACKS]
[GASPS]
I think I have a perfect idea.
This will soften your punches
for smooth knockouts,
like punching a dream.
Quack! Quack!
[SQUEAK! SQUEAK!]
Ha ha!
Meow! Meow!
Pigs on my knees!
[SQUEAL! SQUEAL!]
- That's like math. Yeah.
- Mathematical.
[ALL CHEERING]
What do you think?
Fixed all your problems, right?
No! That was terrible.
Now the men are just
punching animals.
It's worse than before,
and it's in no way
a good solution.
- I'm sorry.
- Well, you should be.
It's not fair to those animals
and it's not fair to me.
I might just start to cry again,
you know?
[SOBBING]
- Oh, man.
- Come on, Jake.
I gotta give this
another shot.
Finn, this guy seems
like a real nutjob.
You know what I mean?
You don't want to get sucked
into this guy's hang-ups.
Yes, I do, Jake.
That's what I vowed --
to help anyone in need,
no matter how
small their problem.
[BOOM! BOOM!]
At least I have to try, brother.
JAKE:
So be it, brother.
[ALL SHOUTING, GRUNTING]
Hey, guys, I'm back.
[ANIMALS BLEAT, SCREECH,
GRUNT AND CAW]
Hey, guys. Guys?
[GROWLS]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Men, men, please stop
for a second.
Aah!
Men! Boys? Please?
I-l have more to ask of you.
[SLAP! SLAP! SLAP!]
Bros? My bros? Brother?
What?
Did you just pet me?
I'll pet you.
Pet, pet.
Hey!
Hey, this is great!
Hey, did you just pet me?
- Yeah! I did!
- Well, I'm petting you back.
W-Whoa.
W-What the...
this is awesome!
[BOTH LAUGH]
All right!
This could be it.
[GRUNTING]
[PAT! PAT!]
[PAT! PAT! PAT! PAT!]
[PAT! PAT! PAT!]
[LAUGHS]
Finn -- ha ha ha! --
you're
really mixing things up
in the best of ways today.
Maybe you can solve
everyone's problems,
like a cherub
with his bottom out.
[LAUGHS]
Okay, cool.
Hey, I'm gonna go
tell the mountain.
All right.
I'm gonna...
Mm! Ahh! Mm!
I'm gonna stay here this time.
[LAUGHS]
So everything's fine
this time, right?
Yes! Thank you, Finn.
So the mountain is totally fine
with everybody petting.
I feel great.
- Right on, man.
The marauders are going crazy
over the petting.
They're petting each other raw.
Check 'em out.
[ALL GROANING]
That's -- okay.
T-That's --
yeah, that's fine.
They look kind of...
rashy.
Hey, Finn!
Hey, man, uh, as you can see,
the petting got sort of...
out of hand.
Stop that!
We are done with that!
We're going back to
roughhousing.
No, wait, fellas.
T-The mountain doesn't like
roughhousing.
Well, we don't like not
roughhouslng.
You see the problem here?
Well, what if...
what if we rotate the entire
mountain 180 degrees around
so the mountain's facing
the other direction?
That way, you guys can keep
roughhousing,
and the mountain
doesn't have to watch it.
Sounds fine with me.
What do you say,
Mountain?!
That's okay.
Only if you guys
promise to stay healthy
and not roughhouse
after you rotate me.
That mountain can talk?
Just promise him anything.
He's out of his gourd.
Uh... yeah, we'll stay
healthy.
Oh-ho! Thank goodness!
All right, kids, spin me
the math around.
Now I just need to set up
some sort of pulley system.
No! Over here!
Don't turn him around!
If you do, I'll miss looking
at his beautiful back.
It's gorgeous!
Huh? What? Really?
What?!
Uh, but -- ugh.
Okay, um, maybe
what we can do is --
BOTH: Excuse me. - Huh?
BOTH:
We need your help.
There's no music playing, and we
desperately want to dance.
Oh, uh, hold on just
a second, you guys.
I'll, uh, I'll help you out
in one minute, okay?
Hey!
Pipe down over there!
I want some peace and quiet!
Uh, let me just, uh --
- I need to be pollinated.
- Huh?
Pollinated all over
to make my babies.
Everybody, please,
one problem at a time.
[GROWLS]
My butt's itchy,
but I can't scratch it.
This water's too cold.
ALL:
Mommy.
Please keep the flies away
from our mommy.
That guy stole our triangle.
They swiped my plum.
ALL: [CHANTING] We
wanna roughhouse.
I'm naked!
[LAUGHS]
What's happening?!
Aaah!
Everybody wants
different things,
and some of them
want stuff
that's exactly the thing
the others don't want.
Whoa, dude, hold on.
So this guy wants this,
and that guy wants that,
but, man,
what do you want?
[DISTORTED]
What do you want?
[SOBBING]
What do you want, baby?
Why are you crying?
[SOBBING CONTINUES]
Margaret, this baby won't tell
me what's wrong with it,
and it's stuck to a leaf
and it stinks.
Give it here, Joshua.
This baby just needs some love
and kisses to be happy.
Mwah! Mwah-mwah-mwah!
- [LAUGHS]
There? See?
Now it's happy.
You just kissed
a boom-boom baby,
so don't expect any more sugar
from me, sweetheart,
until we wash your
dirty, dirty face.
[LAUGHS]
[GASPS]
Hmm.
Jake, what I want
is to help anyone in need
so everyone is happy.
[LAUGHS]
Wow, that's pretty corny, man,
but let's do it, dude!
Whoo-hoo!
Ready over there,
Mushroom Gang?
BOTH:
Ready, Finn!
- Ready, dragon?
- Yes, sir!
Ready, Mountain Man?
[CLEARS THROAT]
I'm ready.
Go!
- [ALL GRUNTING]
[CREAK!]
Hey! The flies are leaving!
[FLIES BUZZING]
[POP!]
Eh! Can't hear a thing.
- Yahoo! Yeah!
- Yay.
Oh!
[LAUGHTER]
Pollen! Here they come!
[CREAK!]
Oh! Yeah!
Yeah-hoo-hoo!
Not naked.
Hey, I can't see anything.
Is anyone roughhousing?
- No.
- Radical.
And I can still see
this gorgeous back.
Thank you, Finn.
You really helped everybody.
[ALL CHEERING]
Stop!
I've got a problem.
Well, what's
the matter?
This dolphin fell
in love with me.
[DOLPHIN SQUEAKS]
That's the opposlte of
a problem.
Adventure time!
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪