[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very
distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Oof! Eef!
Come back, thief!
Whoa!
Stop farting on me!
It's gross!
You can't just go
around stealing boots!
JAKE:
Yeah!
And you know the penalty
for stealing boots --
it's poots on Newts.
[BOTH LAUGH]
[SPLASH]
Uh!
He's getting away
into that lake!
Dude, that isn't a lake.
That's an ocean.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[FARTS]
Woof! Woof! Woof!
[CHUCKLES]
Bark! Bark, bark, bark!
Huh?
[DEEP-PITCHED DRONE]
Uh...
[JAKE FARTING, LAUGHING]
Poots on Newts!
Poots on Newts! No!
[IN SLOW MOTION]
Poo-o-o-ts on Ne-e-wts!
[LAUGHS]
I'm comin', Jake.
I'll poot on that Newt
as soon as I'm barefoot.
Aah!
Uh...
[DEEP-PITCHED DRONE]
[GASPS]
[SCREAMS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GURGLING]
Wha? Ow!
Why is my stomach going nuts?!
Ow!
[CACKLES]
W-w-who are you?
I am the manifestation of
your fear...
Fear of the ocean!
What?!
I'm not afraid of -- of lakes,
wells, rivers, streams,
or deep wells or puddles.
Uh, why would I be afraid of --
Aaah! Uh!
[CACKLES]
'Cause you're a wu-u-ss.
I'm no wuss!
I'm the hero 'round these parts!
Ha!
You're too scared of the
ocean to ever be a true hero.
Not true!
I'm not scared of nothin'!
Aaaah!
[WHIMPERS]
[DEEP-PITCHED DRONE]
Agh!
[SIGHS]
[SNIFFS]
I shall conquer my fear.
[CACKLING]
Yeah, right.
No, I will.
I'll conquer my fear.
Of course you will.
And I live in a two-bedroom
apartment that doesn't
smell like vomit.
[CACKLES]
Sarcasm.
[SIGHS]
JAKE:
Dude.
[PANTING]
Dude, did you see me?
I was all, like, womp!
And then I was all,
like, "Take this!"
Womp! Womp!
And then --
Hey, what's wrong
with you, dude?
Jake, I think I'm
afraid of the ocean.
Say what, now?
I need your help to
overcome my fear.
Will you do it?
Um...
No, I don't really
want to do it.
Jake! Come on!
Heh.
I'm just messin' with you.
I'll do it.
Hmm. Where to start?
Uh, okay.
I think we should just take
a few steps in the water.
You can hold Jaker's
hand if you're scared.
[WHIMPERING]
[THUD]
Um...
Well, that's okay, dude.
I see the problem.
It's just your feet.
Boop. Beep.
Boop, beep, boop, beep.
Beep, boop, beep, boop.
Don't want to be scared.
I shall not be scared.
Boop. Boop.
[DEEP-PITCHED DRONE]
I'm afraid!
Aah!
Jake, get me out of the water!
Now, Jake, now! Now! Aah! Oh!
Oh, oh, oh, aaah!
Hot jam.
You're really scared
of the ocean.
In fact, you're so scared,
it gives me an idea.
Let's start a business of
being scared of the ocean.
Jake!
Okay, okay.
I have a plan to get
rid of your fear.
We'll start tomorrow morning.
But I must conquer this now!
Huaaaaa!
I'm not afraid of you.
[DEEP-PITCHED DRONE]
[IN SLOW MOTION]
Aaaaaaaaaah!
[NORMAL VOICE]
I'm afraid of you!
Aaah!
[SIGHS]
Okay, yeah. Let's try tomorrow.
[JAKE SINGSONG VOICE]
Finn.
[NORMAL VOICE]
Hey, Finn, wake up.
Mornin', Jake.
Ready for me to help you
get over your ocean fear?
Yeah, man.
Cool.
But I can only do
this if you ask me.
I'm askin'.
Then get ready for
my three-step plan.
Watch your troubles melt
away with step one!
[CRASHING]
Aaaaah!
Jake, are you crazy?!
This is not an okay thing to do!
Hey, hey. Come on.
The ocean is your friend.
And you got friends all
around you right now --
[ECHOING]
Miles and miles of friends.
You're nuts.
[GRUNTING]
[NORMAL VOICE]
Don't try to struggle, man.
I'll let you out in a second.
You just need to calm down.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Really? Okay, I'm calming down.
That's great.
You're doing great.
Ready for step two?
Yeah, man. I can do it.
All right, dude.
Step... Two!
Aah!
Jake, this isn't a joke!
It's touching me!
Let it hold you, man!
Let it hold you like a child!
I'm trylng to let it hold me.
[LOUD HEARTBEAT]
Control your breathing.
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
This isn't working.
That means we got
to move to step three.
Just don't scream.
W-what?
I'm gonna push you
underwater with my jowls.
Just don't scream.
Don't scream.
Wha--
Hold your breath, Finn!
You got it, dude!
Aaah!
Get me away, Jake!
Now, Jake! Now! Right now!
Get me away! Aah!
Finn! Stop it! Finn!
Ow!
Yaaaaah!
[WIND BLOWS]
Yaaaaaah!
[SEAGULLS CAWING]
[CHUCKLES]
I'm safe. I'm safe.
How'd I do?
I think we should give up.
What?
I made it all the
way to level three.
Look, Finn, it's not that
I don't want to help you.
I just don't want to
get beat up anymore.
I mean, this is my
bread and butter.
I can't have you messin'
up my bread and butter, dude.
You have to help me.
I can't do this without you.
Okay, fine.
But only if you swear
not to hit me anymore.
I swear I won't
hit you anymore.
And also swear to
only speak in rhymes.
Speak in rhymes all the times.
I swear.
And pigs have hair.
Yes. Perfect.
And since you want more,
it's time for step four.
What?!
I thought you said it
was a three-step plan...
Man.
I'm not that
good at counting.
[CHUCKLES]
Come on.
Let's go kick your fear of the ocean
where the sun don't shine --
In the sea cucumber.
[ECHOING]
Check it, dude.
100% awesomitude.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Yeah, it's pretty math,
you psychopath.
You know, it looks way more
math if you open up your eyes.
Whoa.
See, man?
The ocean is beautiful.
There's no reason to be
afraid of things that are beautiful.
Hey, this isn't that bad.
I'm actually glad.
Hey, look -- a black abyss.
Let's go check it out, sauerkraut.
[ENGINE REVS]
No, Jake!
Turn around! Turn around!
[CACKLES]
[DEEP-PITCHED DRONE]
Aaaaah!
Saying "turn around" twice doesn't
count as a rhyme, dude.
JAKE:
Hey, you swore!
Ow! My bread and butter!
No, dude, don't!
Don't worry, dude.
Everything's cool.
This is the perfect
segue into level five.
Here -- put this on.
[SCREAMING]
Just make sure you don't
pull the emergency tab.
Aah!
No, dude!
I said don't --
Aah!
Oh...
Jake?
Ja-a-a-a-ke!
[BELL CLANGING]
Aah! Jake!
[CACKLES]
Pathetic.
You can't even overcome your fear
now that your friend is about to die.
Your unheroic body will never
let you save Jake.
[CACKLES]
You're right.
What? Really?
You think I'm right?
Well, that's -- that's great.
If my body won't let me
rescue my best friend,
then there's only
one thing left to do.
[AIR HISSES]
[SQUEAK]
No. Wait.
No!
N-o-o-o-o!
[SIGHS]
[GASPS]
[GROANS]
Jake! Jake! Wake up!
Ugh.
You okay, dude?
Yeah, man.
Wait.
Finn! You did it!
You conquered your fear!
What?
You're at the bottom of the ocean!
[FARTS]
Aaaaaah!
Maybe we should
celebrate on land.
[AIR HISSES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
I'm proud of you, man.
You did it.
Thanks, dude.
You've nothing to
be proud of, boy.
You will never get over
your fear of the ocean!
Whoa, dude.
What's with your belly button?
What the flip, man?
I just swam to the bottom.
No, you didn't, cheater.
You just sank to the bottom.
You will never be a great hero.
He's right.
I'll never be a hero.
[GURGLING]
[FARTS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
Finn, you are wrong.
The mark of a great hero ls his flaw.
You know nothing, wisemen.
Silence, Fear Feaster!
We know a lot!
Wait.
Why did you wait so long to tell me?
Because the limo
driver's flaw is being late.
Sorry.
[SQUEAKING]
Farewell, Finn.
You truly are the
greatest hero of Ooo.
[TIRES SQUEAL]
It's time for you to
go away, Fear Feaster!
What?
Am I supposed to live in your
tummy for the rest of my life?
Everybody has a flaw.
And it looks like yours is
smellin' like my nasty guts.
[SARCASTICALLY]
Wonderful.
[CACKLES EVILLY]
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪