[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on,
grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to
very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog ♪
♪ And Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
Yeah!
[LAUGHING CONTINUES]
[PURRS]
Whoo!
Oh, no!
Our sled's broken. Hey!
Let's build one out of snow.
[LAUGHS]
What are you doing, Jake?
R-r-r-r-rah!
[BOTH LAUGH]
Sleds are for suckers.
Just ride on my gut.
[SLOSH! SLOSH! SLOSH!]
Okay! Unh!
Ha ha! Whoo!
- FINN: Yeah!
[BOTH LAUGHING]
Switch!
Whoo!
[LAUGHS]
[MUFFLED]
Switch back!
[LAUGHING CONTINUES]
Penguins!
Whoa!
[PENGUINS QUACKING]
Ha ha!
I'm a flying do-o-o-g!
FINN: [LAUGHS] Mathematical!
What?!
LCE KING:
Who dares enter the lce Kingdom?
Aww.
lce King's here.
You know why I'm here?!
Do you know what
lce King means?!
Yeah, I know what
lce King means --
a big nerd.
[LAUGHS]
Oh! Holy cow.
It means I'm King
of lce, this is my domain, and
you're violating ice world
law -- trespassing!
Come on, brother.
We're just trying
to beat the heat.
Yeah.
There's a big,
sleepy lava man
in our front yard,
and he is so hot.
Mm-hmm.
Wait, wait, no.
I take that back.
L-I mean not like "sexy" hot.
No. No.
You do mean "sexy" hot.
FINN:
No! I mean --
I don't care!
This is my kingdom.
You guys can't just scoot about
on my land willy-nilly.
I've got rules here.
[SIGHS]
Why don't you just
try being cool?
What?!
I am the King!
I am the King of -- of --
[BABBLING]
That's it!
Rise, monsters of snow, and go
beat up Finn and Jake!
Uh-oh.
[LAUGHS]
Whoo!
[SQUAWKING]
Huh?
[SHRIEKS]
Yah!
[WARBLES]
Whoo!
JAKE: Hoo-hoo-hoo, yeah! Ha ha!
Aw, man,
that was great!
[GRUNTS]
You guys are gonna get it.
[LAUGHS]
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, right, sure.
[BLAST!]
[GROANING]
Aw, I need a magic back.
Uh!
[CRACK!]
[SIGHS]
Trail mix.
Yech.
Mmm, yogurt chip.
[CRUNCH! CRUNCH! CRUNCH!]
Tut, tut.
[SIGHING]
Oh, man.
[SINGSONG VOICE]
I'm back home.
Hello, ladies.
[GASPS]
Oh, no! He's back!
He's back.
Oh, my God, he's back.
Oh, my God.
Now, now.
[SINGSONG VOICE]
I brought you
a baby...
and a puppy!
[WHIP!]
[CLANG! CLANG! SMASH!]
[BOTH GRUNT]
Finn! Are you okay?
Huh?
Wildberry Princess?
Hot Dog Princess?
What? I -- what's going on?
We're all prisoners, Finn.
lce King!
What?
Why are you keeping
these girls prisoners, jerk?
You don't understand!
I collect Princesses because I
want to marry one.
Well, why'd you capture
six of them if you just
want to marry one?
I'm collecting them
all first to be sure
I make the right choice.
You're both too young to
understand, but marriage is a
serious thing and lasts forever.
You can't just rush into it,
you know?
Ice King, don't do this.
Just let the girls go.
They don't want to be here.
Of course they do!
I would have killed them already
if they didn't want to be here.
Right, ladies?
[WARBLE! WARBLE!]
Bzzt, bzzt. Uh-huh.
Mm-hmm. Yes.
[SIGHS]
Don't worry, Princesses.
I pledge that Jake and I will
protect each and
every one of you.
And furthermore,
I vow to see
all of you happily married to
whatever sweet
thing y'all want
to be married to.
- Yay!
[GRUMBLES]
Rad!
All I need is something to spear
the lce King with.
Binoculars, toothbrush, water
bottle, rope, sweater,
trail mix...
My flute!
[PLAYS WHIMSICAL MELODY]
Jah!
My flute!
Oh, nuts, dude.
You broke it when we tried
picking the lock to that sad
ogre's heart.
Darn it!
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
♪ Hee hee hee ♪
♪ Hee hee hee hee hee hee hee ♪
Nice try, boy.
Princesses, did you see?
Did you see Finn fail?
Don't worry, Finn.
I'll get us out with...
key hand!
Huh-ha!
Oh, no, you won't.
[ZAP!]
Jake!
Eat it.
I'm -- I'm okay.
Ice King, you had
better either set us free or
come in here and fight me!
'Cause, otherwise, I'm gonna
flip out!
Aaah!
Oh, are you trying to hit me?
Well, excuse me, because I have
to go potty in the bathroom.
[GROWLS]
Ice King!
Finn!
[GROWLS]
Huh?
Jake! You all right?
I'm fine, buddy.
Calm down and tend
to the Princesses.
Oh, my gosh.
I'm sorry, Princesses.
Slime Princess,
are you all right?
He's held us here for weeks,
questioning us about our
favorite sports and
quirky behavior.
I tried to tell him as
little as possible.
I understand.
And, Lumpy Space Princess, uh,
how do you fare?
- I'm bored.
And I'm not having any fun.
LCE KING:
Wha-a-a-t?
Not having any fun?
Last night I read you the story
of Baby What's-it
and the Bottle Prince.
That wasn't fun.
That was lame.
Other Princesses,
do you feel the same way?
[PRINCESSES
MURMURING NERVOUSLY]
When you say "lame, " do you
spell it I-a-m-e?
Well, here, watch.
I'll show you.
We'll have some fun.
Fun's my middle name.
[HUMS AND PLAYS FUNKY MELODY]
Here, now, Wildberry Princess.
I need you to play this.
I don't know how.
Well, come here.
I'll teach you.
Put your hands through the bars.
Atta Princess.
And do...
[HUMS AND PLAYS FUNKY MELODY]
I don't think I can.
Just play it like I showed you.
Leave her alone, lce King!
Play it, or I'll
squish you into juice!!
[SHAKILY]
Oh, dear.
[PLAYS FUNKY MELODY]
Yeah!
Keep playing it.
Now everyone pick up an
instrument and play it.
Oh, this is gonna be so fun!
[GROWLS]
[DRUM SOLO]
[CACOPHONOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
What are you thinking, Finn?
I've almost devised a plan.
I'm gonna let him drum while I
finalize the details in my mind.
- Sweet!
[PANTING]
[HUMMING]
[LAUGHS]
Oh, that was fun!
Hmm.
Ah! it was fun.
Hey, you should go get
some more fun stuff.
You're right.
LCE KING:
Good idea, Finn.
Good idea, indeed.
LCE KING:
I hope they think
I'm fun.
All right.
I've got a plan for how
to get out of here.
First, everyone needs to be
dancing and laughing and saying
fun things like "whoopee!"
Okay?
When the lce King comes back,
everyone play it up like we want
him to come inside the jail and
party with us.
And then, when he steps inside,
wham! --
I'm gonna beat the tar
out of him with these while you
all take care of Jake.
Everyone on board with this?
- Uh-huh.
Sweet!
Nice plan, dude!
I think if everyone's saying
"Whoopee, " the plan won't work
'cause he'll know
we're fakin' it.
Uh, good point, LSP.
I'm gonna say something fun
like, "Oh, yeah, I'm having a
fun time.
Oh, my gosh.
Probably the best time I've ever
had in my entire life."
LCE KING:
Make way for the fun tray.
[PRINCESSES SQUEALING]
Whoa. What's happenin'?
Oh, yeah. Oh.
Probably the best time I've
ever had in my entire life.
Ha ha! So good!
The most fun in the world!
So good!
What is this?
We're having fun.
Whoopee!
[SNIFFLES]
Because I left the room?
Because they like it here.
Because they like you.
Because you're a really fun guy.
I don't get this.
He's not buying it.
Dance harder.
Come on in here and party.
Want to dance with us,
lce King?
Come on!
Really?
You want to dance with me?
Oh, yeah.
Oh. Whoo-hoo! Whoo-hoo!
Wow.
[CLATTER]
Okay!
Yes!
Whoopee!
[SMACK!]
Ohh!
Wait. No!
[WARBLE!]
Don't leave!
I'll kill you all!
[SMACK!]
Ohh!
Why are you doing this?
Everyone was finally
warming up to me.
No!
That is not the case!
You're nuts, man!
And I don't know how to help
you, probably 'cause
I'm just a simple dude.
But maybe you should talk to
someone with more life
experience, like Jake.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Finn, what are you doing?
Don't dump the lce King on me.
But you've got to get
it in your head, man -- putting
Princesses in jail is wrong!
Aah!
Finn, you just ruined my chances
with five or six potential wives!
[WARBLE!]
For that, you will --
[SMACK!]
Ohh! Oh! Oh, my beard.
[CLANK!]
[GROANS]
[THINKING]
Why do people not like me?
Is it because I'm a magic user?
Or is my beard too shaggy?
[SIGHS]
I try so hard to be a good
husband for girls.
What's wrong with me?
[WARBLE! WARBLE! WARBLE!]
Hoo! You're a sociopath.
Who are you?
[LAUGHING]
I know.
You're probably a-a big nerd.
[LAUGHS]
Why don't you try
being cool like me?
Whee-hee-hee-hee-hee-hee!
Oh, space dust is so ticklish.
[LAUGHS]
Heh? What happened?
Princesses?
Ohhh!
[ALL CHEERING]
Thank you for saving us, Finn.
You're welcome, Slime Princess.
And remember when you said
you'd vow to marry us to the
thing of our choosing?
[NERVOUSLY]
Yes.
Well [LAUGHS]
I'd like to marry you.
[ALL "OOHING"]
- Oh.
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah.
Well, about that --
- Jake, help me!
- Oh.
Uh... Slime Princess, you
shouldn't marry Finn.
He pees his pants constantly,
all the time.
Ew!
Oh, gross!
Put me down!
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
I'm sorry.
Jake!
[GROWLS]
[JAKE LAUGHING]
[WHIRL! WHIRL! WHIRL!]
[TING!]
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪