[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
FINN:
Hey, fart face!
Unhand Princess Bubblegum!
Foolish interlopers!
[ZAP!]
Whoa!
Ungh!
- Hee hee hee!
Ooh! My eyesight!
[SQUEAK!]
[CRE-E-E-E-E-AK!]
Huh?
[GIGGLES]
FINN:
Hey, lce King!
I bet you'll never
kiss the Princess!
I wlll kiss her.
I will!
Hold still.
[FINN LAUGHS]
You just kissed
Jake's butt!
What?!
Ugggggggh!
[LAUGHTER]
The hour is yours,
but the day shall be mine!
Just like you, Princess --
Mine!
What a patoot.
Thanks for saving
the day yet again, boys.
You're welcome, Princess.
Uh...
I'm gonna throw
you two a party.
Meet at the Candy Kingdom
tonight!
Party!
Whoo-hoo!
That paper crane
for Princess Bubblegum?
I just thought
I'd bring her a gift
in return for
throwing us this party.
- Heh.
I bet you wish you were my butt.
What?
I bet you wish
you were my butt,
because then
the Princess, you know --
No, wait.
I bet you wish
you were the lce King
and the Princess
was my butt.
- What?!
- Hmmm.
Oh!
I bet you wish Bubblegum
would kiss you, too!
Like the lce King and my butt!
That's ridiculous!
[SMOOCHES]
Ahhh.
Huh? Rrr!
[LAUGHING]
What's so funny?
Hey, everybody.
Finn and Jake are here!
Who's ready to party?!
[LAUGHTER]
What's everyone laughing at?
- Shh!
Stand back, everyone.
This style of massage
is called
"Best Friend Massage."
Oh, my gosh!
Because it can only be done
for friends.
It is completely consensual.
Oh, holy cow.
Relax yourself now,
Lumpy Space Princess.
Hyah!
Oh! I feel so great!
Who is that guy?
- Ha ha!
[FANFARE]
Greetings, partygoers.
Glad you could all make it.
Princess Bubblegum!
Princess, I-l just wanted
to thank you for --
Oh... my... gosh!
PB, you got to check out
this super-cute guy.
You're gonna love him.
- Uh...
This is...
O-oh, my gosh.
I don't even know your name.
Ricardio.
Ricardio at your service.
I've been waiting all evening
to meet you, Princess.
[SMOOCHES]
I've heard you appreciate
ancient technology.
Have you ever
used a balbaflonic laser
to align
the hybernautilus rift
in the boobatron
plasmordial formation?
Whoa!
No, I haven't!
[CALYPSO MUSIC PLAYS]
You want to continue this
conversation on the dance floor?
It would be my pleasure,
Princess.
Why didn't the Princess
invite me to dance?
If you want to dance,
just go dance.
FINN:
But now she's dancing with hlm!
Oh!
I feel... weird!
Eh, it sounds like
you're dealing
with some new emotions
you don't understand --
Like jealousy.
Blaarrrgg!
Look, man, just go out
there and get down!
RICARDIO:
The plasmordial layer is
completely independent
of the babalons.
Dip!
- Wow!
That would mean that
the Babalons would fluctuate
with the piranha
nanosphere.
Correct.
- Ugh!
They're talking
about science, man.
I can't compete with that.
Do the science dance.
Remember it?
It was sort of like this.
♪ Wah-wonh-wenh-anh-enh ♪
You think that'll work?
Yeah! Probably.
Do it, man! You're a pro!
Science dance!
- ...proximity to...
- Science dance!
Hey, Princess, you wanna
spend some time with me?
Excuse me, Princess.
You must excuse me.
Oh. Uh, all right.
Finn! What the cabbage?!
I was learning about Zanoits!
Oh.
I'm... into Zanoits.
T-They're the best!
Zanoits kill hundreds of thousands
of plantoids a year.
Oh, no!
Not the plantoids!
Plantoids produce
mellotoxin.
[BLINK!]
Mellotoxin kills Zanoits!
So, are Zanoits...
good things?
You're totally
jealous of Ricardio.
No, I'm not!
I just don't like
the way he talks to you.
It makes me feel weird.
- That's jealousy, hon.
I'm not jealous!
[ECHOING]
I'm weird!
Woof!
Man, this is going bad!
Hey, Finn,
you got to come help me
slay these peanut
monsters at the bar!
It can't wait!
Wow, man.
What happened out there?
Ugh! I-l don't know.
I was trying
to warn her, but --
but she twisted
my words around.
Yeah,
ladies are twisty, man.
Bubblegum's super-smart, too.
- I know.
And I can't shake this weird
feeling about Ricardio.
I think he's...
a villain.
Why?
Is it because his face is so
foldy and dramatic?
No!
I can just feel it in my gut.
He's up to something sinister.
Maybe what you feel is
romantic rivalry.
- I'll prove he's a villain!
- How?
Stakeout.
Here he comes!
They're talking.
Lemme see.
I can read their lips.
[HIGH-PITCHED] "Hey, shorty, you should
pick your boogers and then fart."
[DEEP VOICE] "You look kind
of like a big pink baguette."
Get serious, Jake!
This is life and death!
Is it?
Don't get me wrong --
I'm all about stakeouts
and spying on this guy,
but what
if he's not a villain?
What if he just looks wicked?
Some people look wicked
but are super-nice.
- I gotta trust my gut.
- Ooh.
He's on the move.
Let's roll.
[GRUNTS]
I see him.
He's holding rope
and going into the trash.
FINN:
He's smashing bottles.
And pretending
to stab someone!
So... he's recycling?
Or what?
I think your gut's
a little naive, Jake.
Holy moly!
He's -- he's with the lce King!
They're shouting something.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Ricardio is tossing him
in the dumpster
and running away!
So I was right!
He ls a good guy -- who's just
cursed to look suspicious.
You and me, gut.
Together forever, solving
crimes and making up rhymes.
No way!
This proves he's a Supervlllaln!
More powerful than lesser
villains, like the lce King.
♪ Your gut says he's evil ♪
♪ My gut says he's good ♪
♪ Why not put our guts together ♪
♪ And end this funky feud? ♪
Then it's settled.
We're gonna confront Ricardio
face-to-face
and prove he's evil.
Or good.
Oof!
So, what are you doing,
Ricardio?
Are you evil?
- Or nice, with an evil face?
That's none of your business.
The safety of Princess Bubblegum
ls my business.
Yeah, we just wanna know
if you're evil or not.
Oh, yeah?
- BOTH: Yeah.
Oh, yeah?!
Yeah! Yes!
You stay away from Princess
Bubblegum with all that stuff!
Now that my plan
is nearly complete,
there's no way
you can stop me.
I could stop you if I wanted!
Oh, yeah?
- Yeah!
Oh, yeah?!
Yeah!!
Yahh!
[GASPS]
What's going on here?!
- Princess?!
- Ricardio?
Yes?
I'm all right, Princess.
Finn, why'd you do it?
He was gonna hurt you
with those ropes and bottles!
These were for our
Balbaflonic laser.
It's not all his fault, Princess.
I might have looked
a little threatening.
Finn, you shouldn't
punch brainiacs.
You know how
fragile they are.
You gotta stop
this jealous business.
- But --
- Come on, Ricardio.
I'll patch you up
and give you candy.
[SIGHS]
She hates me now.
I was totally wrong
about Ricardio.
LCE KING: No, Finn,
you were not wrong.
He ls evil!
[WHIMPERS]
Ice King, what do you
know about this?
Tell me, or I'll do something!
Hold up, Finn.
The lce King looks
sort of damaged.
I don't care.
I only care about Ricardio.
But... my enervated condition
has everything to do
with hlm.
I was trylng to cast a spell
that would glve me
total control
of Prlncess Bubblegum's heart.
But I messed it all up...
[BOOM!]
...and lost control of mlne.
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
He planned to rlp out
Prlncess Bubblegum's heart
to make it hls brlde!
Blblblblblblblbl!
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
Wlthout my heart,
I grew weak.
Ehh!
But I made my way
to the Candy Klngdom
to look for hlm.
In an alleyway, I begged hlm
to return to me
and leave the Prlncess alone.
But then he threw me
in the dumpster
and left me for dead.
Stop... Ricardio.
- Gah!
Come on, Jake!
Gotta save the Princess!
- Princess Bubblegum!
- Princess!
Finn! Jake!
You were right all along, Finn.
Now I'm going to cut out
Princess Bubblegum's heart
and make out with it.
Not if I can help it!
Rarrr!
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
[HORSE WHINNIES]
Whoa!
[GROWLS]
One step closer,
and I'll remove her heart!
Finn, I feel like
a big idiot for doubting you.
He was just so engaging.
But his knowledge on plantoids
is actually pretty weak.
Shut your mouth up, Princess!
[CREAK!]
Oof!
I'm gonna smooch that heart!
It will be my bride!
Why don't you marry
someone your own size?!
Like my foot!
- Huh? Oof!
And my fist!
- Argh! Ugh!
Stop! Stop it!
That's my heart, you piece of...
lce King.
[PANTING]
[GROANS]
Should we... let him
take his heart back?
He is... villainous.
I don't wanna
watch an old man die
on Princess Bubblegum's
carpet, man.
Oh, yeah.
- Wait! Wait!
Come to Daddy.
Yeah, there you go.
- N-o-o-o-o-o-o!
You like that, huh?
See... you...
guys... later.
I feel... wonderful!
Ha ha ha!
And now that
I've saved the Princess,
she'll marry me and live
in my dungeon every day.
- No, she won't!
- Yeah, no, I won't!
Yes, you will!
- Yah!
- Oof!
Well, maybe not today
or tomorrow...
but another day!
Another -- Oyyy!
Ugh! Ugh! D'oh! Enhh!
Thanks again for
saving me -- Agaln.
Don't mention it.
Now that Ricardio's gone,
you don't have to be
jealous of anyone anymore.
I never get jealous.
PRINCESS:
Kiss me, Finn!
[CLEARS THROAT]
[AS JAKE]
I mean, "Kiss me, Finn!"
Am I doing it right, Jake?
- [LAUGHS]
N-o-o-o-o-o-o!
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪