[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on,
grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to
very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog ♪
♪ And Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
Yeah, you think you're
pretty way up there,
but I can get you.
[SPEAKING KOREAN]
All right.
Let me just add
three more drops
of explosive diarrhea...
[POOF!]
BOTH:
Ooh!
Hey, Princess Bubblegum,
when we
bring the dead back to life,
will they be
filled with worms?
No.
If my decorpsinator
serum works,
then all the
dead candy people
will look as young
and healthy as you do.
Ahhhh-ahhhh-ahhhh!
Pick up that platter,
tough guy.
FLNN:
Old Mr. Creampuff?
[GIGGLES]
We used to date.
[SQUISH!]
Something's happening!
Come on! Come on!
Work!
Su... g-g-gar!
Algebraic!
Wait.
Something's wrong.
Sugar!
[SPLOSH!]
BOTH:
Ohh! Aah!
[FWUMP! RATTLE! RATTLE!]
[MOANING]
Whoo-hoo!
[CREAK!]
Hey, look!
The decorpsinator
serum is working.
No! This is wrong!
They're not
coming back to life!
They're still dead!
My decorpsinator serum --
it's incomplete!
Rah!
Must eat sugar!
[GRUNTS]
You're grounded, Mister.
Oh, this is really bad.
They're going to be attracted
to the Candy Kingdom.
Why?
Because the candy people
are made of sugar,
you ding-dong!
Gimme some sugar, baby.
Aah!
Chew on this!
[GIGGLES]
Good one, Finn.
Quickly! To the kingdom!
Get a life!
[BELLS TOLLING]
All citizens of
the Candy Kingdom!
Report to the palace
immediately!
Let's go.
The Princess needs us.
Whoa!
[WHOOSH!]
[CANDY PEOPLE CHATTERING]
[ZOMBIES MOANING]
Hurry, sweet citizens.
All right!
You heard the Princess!
Everyone in!
All right. No pushing.
Come on.
Dude, what's up?
The Princess will
explain everything.
Tree trunks,
get those hot buns
in here, girl.
Oh, I hope it's not bad news.
[CLUNK!]
Did we get everyone?
MAN:
All present and accounted for.
FLNN:
Thanks, Manfried.
You're welcome.
Citizens, we are
assembled here in the candy
foyer for a momentous
announcement.
Tonight, we are all going to
have... a slumber party!
What?!
[ALL CHEERING]
Wait, what about the zom--
go ahead and start partying!
[MUFFLED]
But, Princess, the undead!
We'll be right back, everyone.
Whoo!
Finn, the candy
people can't know
about the zombies.
Wha?!
If they knew, they would flip out!
What do you mean,
"flip out"?
I mean they would
flip out!
Princess?
It's me -- Starchie the
Gravedigger.
I brought you a
larger corpse shovel.
Uh, Princess?
Well, I'll just wait for you
here, then,
by the Mausoleum,
with my back turned and my
defenses lowered.
[SCRAPE!]
[MOANING]
- Huh?
Sugar!
Aaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah!
[POP!]
Candy people explode
when they get scared?!
Not telling the
candy people
about the zombies
is so important
that you need to
promise --
royal promise --
not to let anyone find out about
the zombies --
ever.
Okay. Sure.
No, Finn.
You have to Royal promise.
Yes, I royal promise.
Now, I must
cloister myself
in the lab and
finish the equation to my
decorpsinator serum.
You keep the candyfolk
distracted and ignorant.
Can you do that?
Yes, your highness.
Good.
Don't tell anyone
about the zombies --
never, ever.
Oh, wait.
Can I at least tell Jake?
Tell me about what, dude?
You know, about the
outbreak of zom--
[CHUCKLES]
All right, what's going on?
Uhhh... uh,
nothing at all, buddy!
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
Hey, dude, I think you
and Bubblegum are up to
something.
Aah!
[CHUCKLES]
What? No! No way!
Whoa!
You guys are up to something!
Is it some sort of prank?
Can I get in on it?
Who wants to play
"Truth or Dare"? Hmm.
Okay.
Chocoberry,
you may choose
someone to ask
a deep truth or a
saucy dare.
[FRENCH ACCENT]
Mr. Cupcake, truth or dare?
Dare.
I dare you to take
off your wrapper.
ALL:
Ooooooh!
[LAUGHTER]
Hey, seriously, man,
I'm your bro.
Bros are supposed
to tell bros
everything all the time.
What are you
and Bubblegum up to?
Is everything all right?
Yep -- fine.
Everything is great.
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
[CRINKLE! CRINKLE!]
Except for that. Whoa!
I didn't know
he was chocolate.
Jake,
tr-r-r-r-uth or dare?
Truth.
Do you prefer
chocolate or fudge?
I can't eat chocolate
or fudge 'cause I'm a dog and
they would probably kill me,
but... hmm... probably...
Neither!
Finn, truth or dare?
Dare! Ha ha!
I dare you...
to tell me
the truth about
what's going
on in your mind.
What were you
and Bubblegum
talking about when you
were alone together?
ALL:
Oooooooh!
Umm... uh...
the truth is... uhh...
You promised you
wouldn't frickin'
tell anyone!
Oh, you're so cute, Finn.
Uhhh...
the truth is...
that I'd rather play
"dodge socks"!
[WHIP! SPLAT!]
I'm not playing
"Dodge Socks"
till you stop
dodging my questions. Hey.
[SNIFFS]
Old Mr. Creampuff?
Isn't he dead?
Uh, give me my sock back!
"Dodge Socks"
was a bad idea! Whoa!
Look, dude,
just tell me what's
up, because
you are crazier than
a cannibal tonight.
[THINKING]
Oh, my goodness.
Princess hasn't
finished the equation,
and the
zombies are here!
L, uh...
just want this slumber
party to be super-fun!
And if I did
have something to
tell you,
then I would,
in a second,
and it would make my
life easier,
unless there was
something stopping me,
like a promise,
but there isn't,
so I won't,
so it's cool.
Sugar!
What? You lost me.
Uh... hey...
you know what time it is?
Adventure Time?
No!
Time for
"Seven Minutes in Heaven ."
- You're first!
- Really?!
Lady Rainicorn, in the
closet with Jake!
[SPEAKING KOREAN]
[LAUGHS]
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
Okay, okay, all right.
JAKE:
But in seven minutes,
I'm gonna come out there
and make you
spill your beans, Finn.
I can't hear you all
the way in heaven!
Sugar!
Must eat sugar!
[THUMPING]
Um... does anyone
else hear that?
What?
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
Hear what?
L-I don't hear anything.
[CANDY PEOPLE MURMURING]
I hear something
I don't understand,
and it
makes me scared!
What?! No, Chet.
Everybody wait.
What noise?
You mean...
this noise?
[TECHNO MUSIC THUMPING]
Oh!
[LAUGHS]
Yeah! Dance it!
Bust it up!
Uh-oh-oh!
[MOANS]
[PANTING]
What is this game you are
playing at now, Finn?
Uhhh...
it's "Blockado."
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
The game of barricades.
Come on --
let's block all the
entrances and windows.
[ALL CHEERING]
Blockado!
All right, this is not
a permanent solution.
[GASPS]
Think, Finn.
How can you keep everyone
from finding out?
MANFRLED:
Find out about what, Finn?
Manfried!
The talking piñata!
Your convenient
appearance gives
me a great idea!
Everybody, grab a stick!
New game -- we're gonna
smash some piñatas!
What?!
Except for you, Manfried.
Oh, thank goodness.
Now, everybody don
these blindfolds.
Thanks, taffy girl.
[ALL CHEERING]
All right, everybody,
get together.
I'm hanging the piñatas.
They're all around you.
Smash the piñatas!
[ALL CHEERING]
Yeah! Hwah!
Hwah! Hyah! Wah!
[THWACK! THWACK!]
Yeah!
You guys are on fire!
Ehh!
Mmm! Mmm!
Oh, it is so tasty.
We did it!
My improbable plan worked.
Whew! Annyong!
Seven minutes up yet?
[CHOMP! MUNCH! MUNCH!]
Whoa!
[PANTING]
What the nuts
happened here?!
Oh, we killed all the
zombies that
Princess Bubblegum
and I raised from the dead.
Really?! Huh?
J-Jake?
What's going on?
Wha?
[GASPS]
Finn!
Did you break your
royal promise?!
Yeah, but... l mean, all
the zombies are dead.
The candy people
won't freak out.
What's the big deal?
This is really,
really bad, Finn!
You can't break royal
promises --
never, ever, never,
no matter what, forever!
[RUMBLE!]
The guardians of the royal
promise are coming for us.
[RUMBLE! RUMBLE!]
[CRASH!]
[BOTH SCREAMING]
[ROBOTIC VOICE]
Finn the Human,
you have broken
a royal promise,
for which the penalty
is trial by fire.
[FOOSH!]
That's stupid.
Wait!
He's my friend!
Isn't there another option?!
Yes.
Because you care for the
promise-breaker,
we will give
him a less-hot trial.
You must now answer...
[ROBOTIC VOICE]
Math questions!
Mathematical!
Finn,
you're terrible at math.
Aww!
Now... solve this!
[FWOOM!]
[RAPID BEEPING]
[GROANS]
Oh. Wait, wait.
I thought of a better one.
Yes! "2+2"!
Solve it or die.
Uhh...
4...right?
[BOTH LAUGH]
Oh. Correct.
[RATTLE! RATTLE!]
[SHATTER! SHATTER!]
FLNN:
What's happening, Princess?
You defeated the
broken royal promise!
The gumball guardians
are resetting!
BOTH:
Whoa! Oof!
Slam-a-cow!
That was tops!
Who's not good at math?
I was all, "4!"
4...4, 4, 4...
[GASPS]
That's it!
The answer was
so simple, I was
too smart to see it!
You're welcome.
"4" is the last
figure I need to perfect my
decorpsinator serum.
[TWINKLE! POP!]
Golly!
[CANDY PEOPLE CHEERING]
Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
This is messed up.
But sweet.
[SPEAKING KOREAN]
Uncle chewy!
Grandma!
Former dead relative!
Starchie!
Mornin'.
Man, you broke
a royal promise?
You're nuts.
All's you had
to say was that it
was a royal secret.
I know what's up.
I hope you grasp
the full consequences of
breaking promises.
Heck yeah!
If I break a
royal promise,
I get to fight zombies,
throw slumber parties,
awake gumball guardians,
and -- and --
All right, all right!
And reverse death itself!
Oh, you are adorable.
But keep your promises, okay?
I will, Princess.
[GNAW! MUNCH! SLURP! CHOMP!]
Starchie,
you're not a zombie.
I can't help it.
Flesh is delicious.
You're delicious!
Oh!
[LAUGHS]
Don't squeeze me. I'll fart.
[FARTS]
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies
and bees ♪
♪ We can wander
through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪