[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very
distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
JAKE:
Ha!
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[LAUGHTER]
Here.
Try throwing this one.
Ugh!
[GROWLS]
Here's one called
"Caturday Surprise."
Throw it!
Ugh!
[CATS MEOWING]
[LAUGHTER]
PRINCESS BUBBLEGUM:
Yeah, go on!
Get out of here!
Unless you feel
like a fist cookie,
you better keep running!
What the heck is going on?
I have no idea, but it's probably
best to stay out of it.
Yeah. Hey, look.
This one looks stupid.
Let's see how it flies.
Ugh!
Aw, lame.
Huh?
[GLASS SHATTERS]
Uh-oh.
PRINCESS BUBBLEGUM:
Duke of Nuts!!
What have you done?!
Ohh.
Oh, no.
She thinks that nuts guy did it.
We got to go clear
up what happened.
Don't worry, my dear.
I'll have you fixed
up in no time.
Princess?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I guess if green
and bald is okay.
[GASPS]
[LAUGHING]
Ooh-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo, boy.
I'm sorry.
I can't stop now.
My dear, not to worry.
The medicine milk in this suit will
have you healed lickety-split.
In just five days, you'll be back to
your beautiful Bubblegummy self.
Five days?!
The grand meeting of
Ooo Royalty is tonight!!
[POP!]
Ohh.
[PLOP!]
Uh, hey, Princess.
There's something I should tell
you about that bottle
that hit you in the face.
I already know, Finn.
The Duke of Nuts has
always been a bad guy.
But now that he's done this,
I'll never forgive him!
And it's not just because
I hate the Duke.
I'd never forgive anybody
who did this to me.
I'd hate them...
Yeah, but --
BUBBLEGUM:
...forever!
Forever?!
Finally, I have a witness
to his misdeeds!
Two witnesses.
Jake!
Oh, Finn, my flawless,
flawless champion.
Bring the
Duke of Nuts to justice --
The justice of a cold dungeon!
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
[POP! POP!]
[LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
She's completely bonkers.
What do I do?
If I tell her I threw it,
she'll hate me forever.
Don't worry.
That won't happen.
We're gonna catch that Duke.
But we're the ones
who threw the bottle.
Dude, look.
The Duke of Nuts
is bad guys.
How do you know that?
Think about it.
If Bubblegum
hates him so much,
then he must have
done some rotten stuff.
I mean, maybe he even threw a bottle
and turned someone ugly before.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe I am.
All right, then.
Just this once,
we'll be vigilantes!
Nah, we're more like cops --
crooked cops.
[IMITATES GUN COCKING,
BULLETS FIRING]
Princess, I won't rest until the
villainous Duke is captured!
Oh, thank you, Finn.
[LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
Whoa, okay, and by then, hopefully
you'll have taken care of... this.
Look yonder!
The Duke of Nuts' castle.
Duke of Nuts!
How are you?
By order of Princess --
um... Princess...
[GASPS]
Hello, Finn.
Are you here to arrest the Duke?
How did you know?
The Nuts told me.
For I am the Duchess of Nuts.
[GULPING]
Oh, should have asked if these
were like her eggs or something.
I know of my husband's
crime against the Princess --
a crime that you
personally witnessed!
And why would you lie, huh?
Yeah. Why?
Oh, but he was once
such a wonderful man.
He pet dogs, kissed babies.
We'd lie together underneath
the cashew bush.
He even taught underprivileged
nuts how to dance.
But somehow he's gone rancid!
These nuts tell me
he must be executed.
Would you like to hear what
my nuts have to say?!
That won't be,
um, necessary.
Listen! Listen!
Whoa!
I don't get it, Jake.
How can the dude be evil if he
pets puppies, kisses babies,
and lies with his wife?
What?!
You believe that?
She is nuts.
Listen, man.
Let's just go back
and face the music.
Who cares if Bubblegum
hates you forever?
It's no biggy.
Tons of people hate me.
Why, Jake?
Why won't you print my letters?
L-I-l hate you!!
Hmm.
[GASPS]
It's him --
the Duke of Nuts!
[BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY]
I'll break left!
You take the right!
Ugh!
I went left, too!
Ooh!
Wha?
You're way smaller
than I thought you were.
Dude, that's not him.
No one will harm
the Duke of Nuts.
I will kill whoever
seeks to arrest him.
No! Please!
This has gone far enough.
That's the Duke of Nuts.
But I vowed to kill
whoever did this to you.
They can't take you away, Dad.
[CRYING]
Who's the toughest little nut?
That's you.
[SOBS]
One second.
[CRYING]
Man, I don't know, Jake.
Why would Princess Bubblegum hate
him if he was such a nice guy?
Just because he's a good father doesn't
necessarily mean he isn't a villain.
That doesn't look like a villain.
I could probably think
of a reason why that's
villainous if you gave
me enough time.
Maybe.
- Ugh!
Maybe we should
just confess.
But then Princess Bubblegum
will hate us forever.
Hey, man.
It's not that bad being hated.
Come on! Pick it up!
You son of a blee blob!
Oh. Sorry to make you wait.
I made these daisy crowns
for you guys as a --
as a token of my
gratitude for waiting.
Ohh, sorry, I --
I have to sit down for a second.
Oh.
I know this is an odd question,
but you wouldn't happen to have
any pudding on you, would you?
Actually, yeah,
I think I have one in my pack.
Oh. Oh, thank goodness.
I think I have a
spoon in here, too.
What --
What happened to the cup?
Oh, I'm so embarrassed.
Now you know my shame.
I can't stop eating pudding.
What?!
I don't tell people because
I hate making them worry, but,
yes, I have a rare condition,
a pudding deficiency.
[SIGHS]
And I always end up eating
all the royal pudding supply
whenever I go to the castle.
So that's why
Princess Bubblegum hates you.
Yes, but I didn't turn Princess
Bubblegum green and bald.
I would never do such a thing.
Ugh!
Of course you wouldn't.
You're too nice a guy.
I'm the one who
threw that bottle.
I was gonna tell her, but
then she started talking all crazy.
She said she'd never forgive me,
and I didn't know.
Hey, it's okay.
People make mistakes.
It's all part of growing up.
And you never really stop growing.
Now you're making me feel even
worse by being so nice about it.
Maybe I should just confess
the crime and end all this.
Wait.
I think I might have an idea that will
save everyone's reputations.
Halt!
Finn!
Did you find the Duke yet?
Not yet.
But you are in grave danger,
Princess.
There is an assassin in these very
woods dead set on stopping
you from reaching
the grand meeting.
In fact, it's that
rustling in the bush.
Rustle, rustle, rustle.
JAKE:
I'm an ambush! Halt!
What's going on?!
Oh, did I come out too early?
[CLEARS THROAT]
What are you here to do,
stranger?
I've come for the Princess!
I'm an assassin!
Um, guys...
Stand back!
L will stop him! Hyah!
Hyah!
Phew!
I'll kill you and raise
your children as my own!
[SLOW MOTION]
Hyah!
H-a-a!
Unh! Ugh!
Remember,
it's just acting, Jake.
Sorry, dude.
Ooh!
Now, to kill you up!
But wait!
Surely this cannot be the
fair Princess Bubblegum.
Where are her pink,
flush cheeks?
The long, gooey hair?
- Ugh!
Oof!
Clearly the princess
travels elsewhere.
Later, Bubblegum!
Get out there, man!
I don't know if
I can do this.
Go, go, go, go!
And that's how I,
the Duke of Nuts,
by disfiguring
you beyond all recognition,
humbly saved your life.
Yeah! All right!
Yeah!
What was the point of
this little play again?
[GASPS]
And why isn't the
Duke clapped in irons?
She's right.
Innocent or not, I should accept
what's coming to me.
Peppermint Butler.
Oh, no.
"Nut'n's" going my way today.
Hup!
Hup! Hup!
- No!
Finn?
The Duke didn't
throw that bottle.
Ugh.
Princess, I have something
sucky to confess.
I'm the one who
threw the bottle.
[GASPS]
I'm sorry.
But I knew if I told you,
you'd hate me forever.
Hmm.
Well... l could never stay
mad at you forever.
And you seem
genuinely penitent.
I don't even know what that means,
but thank you.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Yeah!
[LAUGHS]
But that doesn't douse
my hatred for the Duke!
Yeah, what's up
with that hate?
That jerk always empties
out my pudding pantry!
Aw, shucks.
He just can't control
himself around pudding.
He goes coconuts for it because
he has a pudding deficiency.
It's true, your majesty.
I -- I'm sorry for my
medical condition.
Oh, my.
You poor man.
Of course you're forgiven.
Yeah, I don't believe
a word from him.
[SIGHS]
I'm really sorry about making you
temporarily ugly, Princess,
especially before the
Grand Meeting of Ooo Royalty.
I wish there was some
way to make it up to you.
Maybe there is, Finn.
Maybe there is.
[WHISTLING]
Hey!
Hmm? What?
You said "Maybe."
Call to order the sesquicentennial
grand meeting of Ooo Royalty.
I now call upon the delegate
from the Candy Kingdom.
Princess Bubblegums?
[CLEARS THROAT]
"It would be be presumptuous
indeed to present myself against
the distinguished Princess to
whom you have listened."
[YAWNS]
Buy a lady a drink?
[ALL GASP]
The Marquis of Nuts?!
Yes! But I didn't come alone!
Remember me, Jake?!
No.
- [GROWLS]
- [SCREAMS]
[BOTH SCREAM]
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪