[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very distant
lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
Dude, how long are
we gonna follow this frog?
I just want to see him
put on that crown.
Wow!
- Whoa!
JAKE:
it looks cool in there.
Too bad we don't have
the key to this.
What are you talking about?
I got two keys right here.
[LAUGHS]
Unh!
Whoo-hoo!
Ugh!
Wow.
Look at this place.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Jake, are these
doughnuts?
They look like
doughnuts.
But maybe they're
polsonous doughnuts!
- [SNIFFING]
- Yeah, sniff it, Jake!
Suck up those toxins!
Wait a second. I don't know
what poison smells like.
WITCH:
Hey!
[GRUNTING]
Razzamafoo!
- Hey!
- What gives?
You ate one
of my doughnuts!
No, I didn't.
I just sniffed it.
[SHRIEKS]
You're lying!
The stink of magic dog lips
is everywhere!
Holy slug, lady.
Calm down.
Listen, Mrs. Witch --
I never married.
Well, I never ate
your doughnuts.
You -- you're eating one
right now!
I am not.
Whoa!
Huh. That's weird.
I don't even remember
grabbing this.
My subconscious
must be hungry, huh?
Eh, whatever.
[GRUNTING]
Magicus no moricus!
- Uh-oh.
- Aah!
- [COUGHS]
- Dude, are you okay?
Yeah, I think so.
Just a little chilly.
Whoa!
[LAUGHS]
What did she do to you?
I stripped him
of his magical powers.
For stealing one of
your billions of doughnuts?
Yeah, it's not like I killed
your husband or something.
I am not married!
The point is,
you overreacted.
And what gives?
I used to have like eight more
of these things.
The only way
I'll give back your powers
is if you admit your error
and say you're sorry --
and mean it!
'Cause I can tell
the difference.
Well, you can forget it,
because you're the one
who's wrong!
Right?
- Total support, dude.
[GROANS]
Go backicus
from whence you camicus!
Aw, now, you're just
making these up!
Are you all right, my --
my doughnut pretties?
[CHUCKLES]
Wait a second.
You're a bagel!
Liar!
Liars everywhere!
There's got to be a way
to get your powers back!
Where'd they come from,
anyway?
Were you born with them?
Or did you have a freak
industrial accident?!
Heh, that takes me back.
Let me just...
[DEEP VOICE]
remember!
[NORMAL VOICE]
I see a memory.
When I was just a pupster...
I'm rolling around
in a mud puddle.
And I'm just lovin's it.
[GRUNTS]
Oh, no!
Ugh!
[PANTING]
Whew!
Remembering is hard work.
What happened next?
Oh, um, um,
I went into the mud,
and I guess I became
a magic dog?
Okay, then our course
is clear.
We'll roll you in every
mud puddle in Ooo
until we find the one
that'll restore your powers!
That's nuts, man.
You got any idea
of how many mud puddles
are in the land of Ooo?
Four?
Maybe even five?
Jake, come on!
We've always been lucky, buddy.
Maybe the first mud puddle
we find will be the right one.
Nonsense.
But I like it!
Then away!
Yeah, let's do it!
- Ugh!
- Oh, my gosh!
Ugh.
I forgot that I don't have
magic powers anymore.
How do we search for the mud
without my powers?
We run -- run like
energetic little boys!
[PANTING]
This whole time,
I thought running
was some sort
of leg magic.
[PANTING]
Look at me.
I'm running!
[GROANING]
Oh, no.
[THUD]
Grr!
Running... is... evil.
Come on, lazybones.
It's too hard.
I guess you could ride
on my backpack.
[GROANS]
I can't reach.
[CHOKING]
You good, Finn?
You're strangling me
a little, is all.
[PANTING]
Look, there!
Across the river of junk,
there's an ideal mud puddle!
I'll stretch
into a boat!
[FARTS]
Starting to really miss
that old magic of mine.
We can swim
this river easy.
Hup!
Come on, Jake!
[GRUNTING]
Man, that looks
exhausting.
You're right, Jake,
it ls exhausting.
[GASPS]
What are you?
I'm your subconscious!
Okay.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to tell you
that what you're feeling
deep down inside is true.
It ls way too hard to swim
across the river.
It's easier to wear a hat.
Here, have a hat.
Heh, heh!
BOTH:
Yeah!
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Man, I'm glad
I met you.
Jake, stop talking to yourself!
Cross over, already!
Uh, I can't swim that
river, dude.
My subconscious says
it's too hard.
Check out this hat, though.
Grrr!
What's wrong with that guy?
Then just wait for me there!
[GRUMBLING]
Stupid...
What you working on,
Finn?
[GRUNTING]
Doing everything!
Look at you,
doing stuff.
Oh, is it a chair --
a chair for my butt?
Whoa!
Ugh!
Mudventure!
Did it work?
Oh, yeah, I can feel
this working.
In fact, you should roll
in the mud with me, Finn!
We can both be magic!
Yeah!
[BOTH LAUGHING]
This isn't working at all.
This isn't the right
mud.
I was just really hoping this
was over and done.
[SIGHS]
Okay.
Then let's just go find another
mud puddle.
Actually, feeling kind
of chubby-tired.
Can't we do this tomorrow?
Ugh!
This is stupid!
Just go back to the witch
and apologize
and get your powers
back.
Never!
I'd rather be powerless forever
than apologize!
I'm lazy but prideful.
You're not even trying,
man!
First you won't run,
a-and now you keep --
and -- a-and no matter what
I just -- you just -- you...
Adventuring is too much
hard work for a bro
without his powers.
But you are
an adventurer.
Nah.
From now on, I'm just your
regular old dog.
Ironic, given my current
man-baby body.
[BOTH GASP]
Behold, the beautiful mermaid
of the river!
Ugh!
Which one of you mortals
wants to mate with all this?
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, um... how do I say,
"you're the grossest thing ever,"
without offending you?
Grrrr!
I'll scare her off,
Finn.
[BARKING]
How do we beat power
like that?
- Finn, I've got an idea.
- What is it, buddy?
Rub my belly!
Yeah, I'm one of those
kind of dogs.
Grr! Yah!
[LAUGHS]
[LAUGHING]
Finn?
Finn!
Come on, Finn!
You got to save yourself!
I'm just a dog!
Aw, man.
Oh, geez.
Okay, then I'm back
on the team!
[GRUNTING]
I'll save you!
Jake?
Don't worry!
Hey, Finn, can you help me
to get up there?
ALL:
Hungry, hungry, hungry.
Ohh.
If only I had my powers back!
The only way I'll give back
your powers is --
I know, I know!
I have to apologize
to that witch.
Oh, you're doing so well.
[GRUFFLY]
And I hate you so much.
Hey! Witch!
I need my powers back!
So I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry
I ate your doughnut!
Razzamafoo.
Huh?
Uh, oh.
So, do I get my powers back?
[NORMAL VOICE]
Mmm. Apology denied.
What? Why?!
Because you took too long.
Now you have to apologize
while doing
a variety
of humiliating things.
No way, Jose!
Come on, dude.
It's the only way to save Finn.
- Who is that?!
- He's my subconscious.
Then he has to do it, too.
Aw.
L...
Jake the dog...
while slow-dancing
with my subconscious...
With flowers
in my underwear...
do humbly
apologize.
Wait, wait.
Start over.
- You're recording this?
- It's for my newsletter.
No way.
I have my dignity.
Then guess what, cool guy --
you can forget about getting
your powers back -- ever!
Oh, no, dude, what do
we do now?
[COUGHS]
Oh!
I'm dying, Jake.
- What?
- He says he's dying.
Let that be a lesson
to all you cupcakes.
Why are you dying, bro?
Because I'm the subconscious
of your old magical self.
[COUGHS]
Goodbye, Jake.
No! No!
[CRYING]
So, I've finally broken you.
Yeah!
[CRYING]
If only I were a humbler guy,
my subconscious
would be alive,
and my best bud wouldn't be
trapped in a mermaid's nest!
Yes!
Gloat, gloat, gloat!
All right, I think you've
learned your lesson.
I forgive you.
My powers!
How can I ever thank --
Ha! Got your cane!
Aah! Ugh!
But didn't you learn your
lesson?!
Nope!
[BOTH LAUGHING]
ALL:
Hungry, hungry!
Aah!
Remember to save the brain
for dessert!
JAKE:
Honey, I'm back!
How about a big kiss?
[SMOOCHES]
Aah!
You guys are so cute,
I could
just maul you to death.
[ALL SQUAWKING]
- Jake!
I never should have
doubted you.
Well, I'm glad you
learned your lesson --
that in a crunch, there's nothing
I wouldn't do for you.
Ahh! So, is that how you got
your powers back?
You apologized to the witch?
Um, no way!
L, um -- I must have found
the right... mud puddle.
Yeah, I-l don't remember.
Heh.
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪