[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on,
grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to
very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog ♪
♪ And Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
FINN:
Candy party!
Jake,
this party is so crazy!
I know, Finn.
I know.
[LAUGHS]
GIRL:
So, Finn, do you have a girlfriend?
Oh, my gosh,
I can't believe
you just said that!
[LAUGHING]
What a wonderful,
marvelous party!
Okay, I'm gonna do it.
Okay, okay, okay.
Everyone watch!
I'm gonna do a flip!
[GRUNTS]
Whoa, oh, oh!
[CRUNCH!]
Ohh! Oh, no!
[LAUGHTER]
[CRACKING]
♪ Dee, dee, dee, ♪
♪ Dee, dee ♪
Whoo, whoo!
[SCREAMING]
Princess Bubblegum's
in trouble!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SMACK!]
Watch where you're going!
[SCREAMING]
[WHOOSH! WHOOSH! WHOOSH!]
[GRUNTS]
Holy cow!
Is the Princess okay?
Ooh!
Please, calm yourselves,
my people.
I am safe!
Oh, thank you, Finn.
You truly are my hero this day.
Cool.
Hero. Hmm.
He-e-e-e-ro.
Hey, I just thought
of something!
Uh, what did you think of?
I'll show you.
Come on.
We'll go through
my secret entrance.
All right, everyone.
Turn around.
Well, turn around!
This entrance is secret!
Oh!
Secret entrance.
Got it.
Math.
Hurry, Finn!
[LAUGHS]
No way!
[BOINK!]
Here it is.
Check it out.
A magical globe?
No, Finn.
It's what you can see
through the globe.
Golly.
[GIGGLES]
Look. You see this book?
Yeah, I see it.
It's called the Enchiridion.
It's a book meant only for
heroes whose
hearts are righteous.
[POOF!]
Shmow-zow!
The book lies at
the top of Mount Cragdor,
guarded by a manly Minotaur.
It's waiting for a truly
righteous hero to claim it!
Do you think I've got
the goods, Bubblegum?
'Cause I am into this stuff!
Yeah, I know.
And, yes, I do.
Then off I go!
Huh?
Ja-a-a-a-a-a-ke!
[CREAK!]
Thanks, pal.
Farewell, Fi--
Oh, wait a minute.
Farewell,
Finn the human boy!
Bye, princess!
You know what time it is,
buddy?
A-a-a-dventure time?
Yeah, man!
[WHIRL! WHIRL! WHIRL!]
[TING!]
[MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS]
Greetings,
young heroes to be.
This mountain
is called Cragdor.
Its purpose is
twofold --
to protect the
Enchiridion and to
test the hearts
of those who
seek to possess it.
Many noble
challengers have
entered,
attempting to pass the
grueling trials
that lie behind
these walls,
but no one has ever
left here alive or dead.
Only the truest,
most worthy
hero can receive the hero's
Enchiridion and walk
out these doors again.
[SNIFFS]
If it is you, friend --
ooh-hoo,
and I cannot say
that I am certain,
but you are verily
welcome to try.
However, first you
must pass my riddle.
My name is Keyper,
and duly so,
for I carry the
key to this door.
But all is not how
it appears, you see.
Or perhaps you don't see at all.
[LAUGHS]
Perhaps the key is in you,
child, but you cannot
use your brawn here.
The door is magically sealed!
[DOINK!]
Ooh, you've unlocked
the riddle and the door!
Ha ha,
brilliantly done, child.
[FARTS]
[BOTH LAUGH]
Please,
reveal to me how you
unraveled my clue.
I just thought you'd
look cute stuffed
in that lock.
Oh, yes.
That's how most people get in.
- Bye!
You've passed the first trial,
young heroes,
but prepare yourselves,
for there are many
trials ahead of you.
And each trial is more
treacherous than the last.
[CLANK!]
[BOING!]
[SNIFFS]
The Enchiridion is...
...that way.
What?!
Dude, you can't smell
the book from here!
It's in the castle on
top of the mountain.
[SNIFFS]
In a room.
[CHUCKLES]
Wish you had one, huh?
VOICES:
Help! Help! Oh, help!
This way!
What about the book?
It can wait.
Someone needs our help.
[GRUNTING]
Yo, Finn, are you all right?
Did you get brain damage?
I'm fine. Keep going.
We have to hurry.
Help! Save us!
We're stuck in the fire!
I've got you.
Thank you for saving us.
Now we can destroy
this old lady.
♪ La la la-la ♪
What?!
[ZAP! POW!]
Anytime you say,
"What?"
We'll destroy an old lady.
What?!
It's a wonderful day.
[ZAP! POW!]
Every time you say,
"No,"
we'll destroy an old lady.
No! What?!
[ZAP! POW! POW! POW!]
Please... ohh!
...don't destroy... ooh!
...any more... aah!
...old women.
Every time you look sad,
we'll destroy a big old woman.
Well, ever since I got to --
[ZAP! POW!]
[SCREAMS]
Hey, guys,
every time he's a
big wuss,
let's destroy an old lady.
[LAUGHING]
Yeah.
Hey, back off,
you gnomes!
That kid just
saved you guys.
You should thank him,
not destroy old ladies.
Do you even know what
I'm talking about?
Say, "Thank you."
Say... thank... you!
Kill him!
[ZAP! POW!]
[WHIRL! WHIRL! WHIRL!]
Get back in there!
Help! Help!
Please, help!
JAKE:
Hey, Finn, you okay?
FINN:
No way, dude.
Those old ladies
are destroyed
because of me.
I'm not righteous.
I'm wrong-teous.
Stupid-teous.
[SPLASH! SPLASH! SPLASH!]
Ah, don't let those
gnomes and their
illusions get you down.
They're just gnomes
and illusions.
Illusions?
Yeah, man.
Think --
what would regular old
sweet ladies
be doing wandering
the hills of Mount Cragdor?
Maybe they're lost?
[LAUGHS]
No way.
This place is
designed to mess
you up,
to mess with your head.
None of this is real.
It's all just trials to test
your heroic attributes.
Hmm.
Hmm!
Now let's go get that book.
Yeah, you're the
smartest dog I know, man.
[LAUGHS]
[CHOMP! SLURP!]
Jake?
[GULP!]
Ja-a-a-a-a-a-ke!
You cannot pass.
Give me back my friend!
- No.
It's okay, Finn.
I can get out.
Let Jake go, or I'll --
I'll kick your foot!
[LAUGHS]
It is impossible
for you to hurt me.
[LAUGHS]
Don't worry, dude.
I found another way --
Huh?
I'm coming, buddy!
[BELCHES]
I think your
dog finally fell
into my stomach.
Hey, where did you go?
I got your wallet, man!
No! My big money!
Give it back!
Give me back my friend!
But I killed him already.
[GROANS]
Fine.
I'll give you your dollar.
Here's your
dolla-a-a-a-a-a-r!
[GROANS]
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa!
Jake!
You're okay!
Stomachs are weird.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Yea-a-a-a-a-a-a-h!
Dude, you just flew us
all the way to the top!
Wait a minute.
[SNIFFS]
I can smell the book right
through this door.
[CRYING]
You're under
arrest for stealing
my dollar!
[CRYING]
Just a minute, Jake.
[GRUNTING]
[WHOOSH!]
Hey!
[LAUGHING]
You know what that was?
That was righteous.
Thanks, Jake.
Now sniff out that book for me.
You got it.
[SNIFFING]
[DOOR CREAKS]
Whoa!
Cool!
MAN:
Congratulations,
Finn the Human.
You must be
truly righteous to
have made it this far.
Thank you.
Now enter my
brain world, and
I will show you
some aspect of
yourself that you're not
entirely aware of.
Where... am I?
GHOUL:
For your final trial, slay
the beast!
Why?
Is it an evil beast?
Ye-s-s-s-s-s.
It's completely evil.
Will you slay it?
Shoot, yeah.
I'll slay anything that's evil.
That's my deal.
[ZAP!]
[WHIP!]
[GRUNTING]
[SPLURT!]
Ye-e-e-e-e-e-e-s.
You've done well, hero.
FINN:
Thank you.
Now, as one last last trial...
[TING!]
...slay this ant!
Is it evil? No!
But it's...
not good, either.
It's, uh, neutral.
Will you slay it?
[CREAK!]
No!
If you want the hero's
Enchiridion, then slay
this unaligned ant!
Never. Never. Never!
Uh-oh.
Hyah!
KEYPER:
Congratulations, Finn the human.
Now you have truly
reached the end --
Never! Ohh!
Oh, no.
Mr. Keyper, I'm sorry.
W-why are
you wearing that
little devil costume?
These are my pajamas.
I was getting ready for bed.
Finn, Jake!
You made it!
Are you another trial?
Trial? Oh, no.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm Manish Man,
the Minotaur.
[GASPS]
The manly Minotaur from
Princess Bubblegum's story!
[LAUGHING]
[MUSCLES CREAKING]
So... can I check out
the Enchiridion?
Can I, can I, can I?
Yeah, come on.
Let's go check it out.
Whoo-hoo!
We've been
watching you guys on
our magical viewing globe.
Take a seat, guys.
Have some juice.
There's grape and apple,
and the
gatekeeper made spaghetti.
And... all right, Finn, are you
ready for this?
[CREAK! CREAK!]
[IMITATES EXPLOSION]
The Enchiridion!
You deserve it, Finn.
Really?
Yeah, Finn, you're the
goodest of
heart and most
righteous hero
I've seen here.
Tenderness,
ingenuity, bravery,
nard-kicking ability,
and when
you took that giant Ogre's
dollar -- oh, man --
the Keyper
nearly fainted!
[LAUGHS]
It's true!
[BOTH LAUGH]
[LAUGHS]
Hey,
crack open that book and
read something,
for fun's sake,
all right?
Oh, yeah. Wow.
"How to kiss Princesses"?
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
Whoa.
What did you just read?
[WHOOSH! TING!]
Yeah, what does it say, Finn?
Manish man won't tell me.
Hey, don't tell her, Finn.
It doesn't say anything,
Princess.
Manish Man!
Oh, ye-e-e-e-e-ah!
[POP! POP!]
[WHIRL! WHIRL! WHIRL!]
[TING!]
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪