[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very
distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
[SCREAMING]
FINN:
[SINGING IN AUTOTUNE]
♪ Baby ♪
- JAKE: Mm!
♪ L know what you need ♪
What's that?
♪ You want your little
baby socks ♪
♪ For your little baby feet ♪
- Whoo!
- ♪ Baby ♪
- Yeah?
- ♪ L know what you crave ♪
- Oh, yeah? What's that?
♪ You want to poop your
pants all day long ♪
♪ Well, baby, behave ♪
Hey, how can you sing
like that, dude?
Remember when I swallowed
that little computer?
Oh, yeah.
All right, Stanley, you
and your family are safe again.
Seriously, Stanley,
for a watermelon,
you get into trouble way more often
than you should.
[WHISTLING]
- W-Whoa!
- What the?
Shmow-zow!
Look at that!
JAKE: That is the most adorable
thing I have ever seen.
And he loves your baby song!
Sing some more of it, dude!
All right.
[AUTOTUNED] ♪ Baby,
you're looking so good ♪
♪ You're looking like you might
want some baby food ♪
JAKE:
Keep it going, man!
♪ Baby, you're looking
so fine ♪
♪ You're looking like you might
just start crying ♪
[LAUGHS]
Yeah!
Dude, this guy is
a pal for life!
It looks like he's got two
jiggly bellies stuck together.
I've got that
on my back.
I call it my butt.
Whoa!
He's the Jiggler!
[BOTH LAUGH]
You are the best thing ever!
Let's take the Jiggler back
to the house
and just stick him by our bed
so we can wake up...
BOTH: next to a little
dancing guy every morning!
[AUTOTUNED]
♪ I gotta tuck you in, girl ♪
♪ L gotta sing you sweet
melodies about babies ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
- Little baby feet!
Welcome to your new
home!
Feast your eyes
on everything!
[WHISTLES]
Nice, huh?
[GRUNTING]
What are you doing?
Splitting my toothbrush in half
so he can use half.
Here you go.
It's for your teeth.
Like this.
[SWISH! SWISH! SWISH!]
Yeah, you got it!
Enough hygiene.
Let's get to it!
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYS]
Yeah!
Toothbrush dance!
Ha ha, this is cool!
- Yeah!
Ahh!
[LAUGHS]
Yeah!
Dance, dance.
[YAWNING]
Dance.
I'm not tired.
How about you, Jake?
Maybe we should go upstairs.
You can have the comfiest spot
on the bed.
Good night.
[WHISTLES]
Morning, Jake!
[YAWNS]
Morning.
Are you ready to get
down?
[AUTOTUNED] ♪ Let's get
this party started! ♪
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah, okay.
[NORMAL VOICE]
Where's the little guy?
Over there.
[SQUEAKS]
Hey, pal, you ready
to cut loose?
Wake and shake, buddy.
Let's do this thing!
[WHISTLES]
[WHISTLES WEAKLY]
Slam-a-cow, that fool
looks rumped.
What do you mean?
Well, look at him.
He's all limp...
and weird.
Uh, I bet he just needs
some breakfast
after a night
of extraordinary jiggling.
Hey, let's combine everything
we can find in the kitchen
and have the Jiggler drink it!
That'll wake him up!
And then we can...
[AUTOTUNED]
♪ Get down! ♪
[WHISTLES WEAKLY]
He doesn't want to
drink that goop, man.
Then let's just give him some,
uh, purple whatevers.
You mean the grapes?
Yeah, whatever.
[GULP!]
Hey.
I think he's digging it!
[HIGH-PITCH HUMMING]
That doesn't sound
good.
[SCREAMS]
Uh...
[HUMMING CONTINUES]
Uh, you think we --
think we fed the wrong hole?
Nah, he just doesn't
like purple whatevers.
What we need to do is figure out
what he does like to eat.
Here, Jiggler.
What kind of food do you like?
Meat? Some banana?
This looks like corn, I think.
A hot dog.
Stanley the watermelon.
Look, Jake! He likes it!
[GASPS]
Wow!
No way!
[SLURP!]
His favorite food is
drawings!
Awesome!
Holy fig, that's
awesome!
What food are you drawing now?
I'm drawing a picture
of you.
Well, don't feed it me!
[LAUGHS]
Come on.
Eat him up, Jiggler.
[SLURP!]
No!
Aah! Aah! Keep it away!
Shoo! Shoo! Aah!
No! Aah!
All right, all right.
I got it. Calm down.
I'll eat him.
Ahh!
Dude, you eating me
is just as bad
as the Jiggler
eating me!
Well, you gonna eat
yourself, tough guy?
Yes, if that is what
must be done.
[MUNCHING]
[GULP!]
I taste awesome.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Okay, all right.
Now, let's get back
to some jiggling!
I'll get the tunes!
[WARBLING]
Like this!
Yeah! Ha ha! Whoo!
Come on, Jiggler!
Wiggle and whistle!
Yeah, Jiggler!
Go nuts!
Go nuts like there's bugs
on your butts!
[MOANING]
[GURGLE!]
[POP! SQUISH!]
Whoa.
[GASPS]
Jiggler?
What the heck?
What's wrong with him?
Uh, there's nothing
wrong with him.
We just got to plug up
his holes.
See? That worked.
Ready to jiggle again,
little guy?
Whoa!
Oh, man.
Quick!
We got to plug those holes!
Jake, hurry!
All I can find is your
glass-eye collection.
What about your
eye-patch collection?
Oh, man, they're in
mint condition.
Jake!
- All right, coming!
Mama, mama,
mama, mama, mama.
One more patch!
Eh! Finished!
Ugh. He looks terrible.
Finn, I know you don't want
to hear this,
but I think we should
cut our losses
and bring this fella back
to where we found him.
We can't just abandon him.
Look at him, Jake.
He needs us now
more than ever.
We just need
to take better care of you
from now on, right,
little guy?
[RUMBLE! RUMBLE! SPLAT!]
Jiggler!
[WHISTLING]
- Oh.
- Wha--
Finn? Okay.
[SCREAMS]
Our pet exploded.
[SCREAMING]
Maybe we can scrape him
up and...
ugh.
[GASPS]
Oh, holy moly!
Don't worry, Jiggler!
We'll fix you!
[WHISTLES]
Pbh-t-t-t-t-t!
Let's gather him up,
Jake!
He's all over the place, even
between the floorboards!
- And the cupboards!
- And the galoshes!
I wonder...
where's his heinie?
[SQUEAK! SQUEAK!]
Found it! Come here, you!
Hey! Ugh!
Come on, let's put him
back together.
- Okay.
- Squeeze real hard.
He's slipping!
- I got him.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Well, at least
he's all in one piece.
Sheesh, you think he's...
dead?
No way!
I won't let you die, guy!
Not this time!
[BLOWING AIR]
[SMOOCHING]
Finn, stop it, man!
What are you doing?
I'm kissing him!
What do you think?
That's all I can think to do.
Just put him down.
[SLOOP!]
[SMOOCHING]
He's kissing colors
with his dying breath.
I think he's trying
to tell us something.
Finn, this looks like it could
be his mom!
[WHISTLES]
We took this child away
from its mama, Jake!
We're kidnappers and murderers.
I just wanted to have fun
and jiggle!
Look, chill out, okay?
We can fix this.
Check it out.
His mom looks like she's out
by Stanley's house,
where we found the Jiggler.
If we get him back to her,
she'll be able to fix him up!
Then there's no time
to spare!
[WHEEZING]
Shh.
Just hold on a little longer,
buddy.
[WHISTLING]
Did you hear that?
Whistling!
Perpendicular!
It's the mama!
[ALL WHISTLING]
[WHISTLING]
Look, the little guy
wants to go home!
Well, this is it,
buddy.
Be well.
[WHISTLING CONTINUES]
[SNIFF, SNIFF]
[SCREECHING]
Hey!
Stop that!
Huh!
I don't understand.
That crazy mama
almost killed him.
He feels cold.
What are we supposed
to do now, man?
We can't bring him home
or he'll... or he'll...
- Pbht!
- Dang it!
Why doesn't she love him?!
I love him! You love him!
It's not fair!
[SCREAMS]
- Finn, wait!
Mama's supposed to love
baby!
She's supposed to love baby!
Huh?
[SNIFFLING]
Oh, man!
It's yours, idiot!
[GROWLING]
Don't you recognize
your own baby?!
Finn!
I figured it out, dude!
It's the juice!
The Jiggler needs to smell like
its mama's juice.
That's how wild animals
know what's going on.
And this guy right here
is all drained out.
We got to toss it
in the soup, brother.
All right. Okay.
I loved you, baby.
I hope you know that.
Word to your mothe-r-r-r-r-r-r!
[SPLAT!]
[WHISTLING]
[SNIFF, SNIFF]
BOTH:
Aww.
I'll never kidnap
again.
You said it.
That was a nightmare.
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪