[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to
very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
[FINN AND JAKE CHEERING]
- Yah!
- [SCREAMS]
Whoo, swords!
Yeah, swords!
Swords! Whoo!
Oh, men and their swords.
You boys stop horsing around
with my apples.
BOTH:
Aw, Tree Trunks.
Now, come on on over.
I baked y'all an apple pie.
- JAKE: Yeah! Whoo-hoo-hoo!
- FINN: Whoo! Apple pie!
I'm gonna eat it all
before you even get there!
Noooooo!
[HUMMING]
Apple pie.
- Don't let him eat it all!
- [LAUGHS]
Now, you boys behave
yourselves and sit down.
Ohh!
Shoo, fly!
Get off my apple pie!
Ugh!
A fly landed on my pie.
That's no good.
Bye-bye.
Why are you throwing
the pie away?!
BOTH:
Ugh!
Flies wanted it,
they can have it.
[OVEN BELL DINGS]
Anyways, don't y'all worry,
'cause a new pie's coming
in a wag of a lamby's tail.
BOTH:
New pie? Yeah!
Whoo-hoo! Pie! Yeah!
Here ya are.
- Whoa!
Come on. Go ahead.
[BOTH MUNCHING LOUDLY]
What'd ya think?
Best apple pie ever!
Oh, Jake.
Thank you, but that isn't
the best apple pie.
What are you talking
about, Tree Trunks?
What could be better
than your apple pie?
You ate all the pie.
Finn, what would you do
if you could do anything?
Anything?
Well, I'd catch a shooting star
and travel to outer space
and fight space monsters.
I'd carve my face on the moon
so the moon would
look like my face.
What would you do,
Tree Trunks?
I would go pick an apple.
Lame.
[SMACK!]
I-I'm sorry.
L-I mean, it's just that
you pick apples every day.
This apple ain't like
the apples that I pick.
They say it's the apple
of apples,
rarest kind of all.
Legends call it
the crystal gem apple.
Ugh!
- That sounds awesome!
- Where is it?
I heard that it grows
in the deepest end
of the evil dark
forest.
Whoo! Tree Trunks, you got
to go pick that apple.
Yeah!
What? Me? Oh, no.
I'm just a cute little elephant.
I'm not cut out
for adventuring.
Tree Trunks, this is your dream.
Think about eating that apple
with your own mouth.
Or your trunk!
Imagine the flavor.
And your satisfied face!
Really? You think I can handle
the scary dark forest?
Yeah! And we'll help you.
We love you, Tree Trunks.
Okay, I'll do it.
Call me
Adventurer Tree Trunk.
Yeah!
Tree Trunks!
I love being so high
up from the ground.
[CHUCKLES]
Psst.
I could take you even higher on
my shoulders, Tree Trunks.
No, Jake.
She has a weak heart.
Oh, yeah.
Ew!
Why is this ground all squishy?
Whatever it is, I'm liking it!
Oh, yeah!
I want to try. Okay.
I'm cool with letting you do
whatever you want.
[LAUGHS]
It's like some cookie dough.
[GROWLS]
Oh. Hello, there.
Huh?
Uh, Tree Trunks,
stay away from that.
BOTH:
Aah!
Aah! Unh! Ugh!
You're gonna get it,
wall of flesh!
Yuh! Yuh! Yuh! Yuh! Yuh!
Yuh! Yu-u-u-h!
An eye.
And a mouth.
Well, I think I've got
the perfect thing
for him or her.
Stickers!
- [GASPS]
Careful, Tree Trunks.
This thing is evil.
Here's a rainbow sticker.
[GROWLS]
And here's
a scratch-and-sniff sticker,
smells just like a pickle.
Oh.
And this one's
a holographic unicorn.
But it doesn't have a horn.
Oh!
Now, what you doin'?
Huh?
Tree Trunks!
Ha-a-a-a-a-ah!
[SCREAMING]
You better stay in that tree,
baby!
Tree Trunks,
were you putting stickers
on that evil monster?
- Yes.
L-I thought it needed some
tender love and affection.
Oh!
What a pretty butterfly.
[LAUGHS]
Tree Trunks?
[SIGHS]
Jake, I just realized
that Tree Trunks
is old and bonkers.
We can't take her through
that evil dark forest.
Ah, she'll be fine.
Everything's fine.
- But the monsters.
- It's fine. it's fine!
Are you sure?
'Cause she has
zero adventurer training.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's fine. She'll be fine.
L-I-it's fine. it's fine.
It's fine.
[LAUGHS]
Maybe it ls fine.
Tree Trunks?
Where'd she go?
FINN:
Tree Trunks?
TREE TRUNKS: [LAUGHS] Oh!
[SIGNPOSTS GROWLING]
We got to find her, Jake.
Tree Trunks!
Where are you, Tree Trunks?
And here's your teacup,
and here's my teacup.
BOTH:
Tree Trunks?
[BOTH GASP]
And here's your sandwich.
- [GROWLS]
Oops, you dropped it.
Tree Trunks! Run!
Oh, hey, Finn.
Hyah!
Time to call your mamas,
evil signposts.
[GROWLS]
[GRUNTING]
Patience, boys.
There's enough tea for everyone.
[GRUNTING]
No!
Oh, what a nice hug.
[GRUNTS]
I'm not hugging you!
I'm trying to [GRUNTS]
save your life!
[GRUNTS]
There's too many!
Finn?!
[GROWLS]
[WHOOSH!]
Oh, Finn.
That tea party was crumbier
than a big ol' biscuit.
Aah!
Tree Trunks, I'm all jacked up
because of you.
Look at my jacked-up face!
Are you mad at me?
[SIGHS]
No. I'm not mad at you.
You're too supercute for me
to be mad at you.
And you're a topnotch
adventurer.
Now, let's go find
and eat the heck
out of that crystal gem
apple together.
[HISSING AND GROWLING]
Dang it!
You go fight.
I'll keep Tree Trunks
out of trouble.
Awesome!
[GRUNTING]
Uh, Jake, I think Finn's
getting jacked up again.
Yeah, Finn can handle it.
He's 12.
I think I know
a way to help him out.
Uh, you should stay here,
Tree Trunks.
But Finn said I was
a topnotch adventurer.
And my adventurous
instincts tell me
to seduce that tentacled critter
with my womanly charms
and elephant prowess.
Uh, no way.
[GRUNTING]
Huh?! What are you doing here,
Tree Trunks?
Wha! Ugh!
I'm helping you by tempting
this guy with...
[SEDUCTIVELY]
my body.
It's not a guy, Tree Trunks!
It's a snake-armed
ruby brain beast.
Even brain beasts get lonely,
Finn.
Jake, you were
supposed to watch her.
She got past me, man.
I tried to stop her,
but she overpowered me.
Get her out of here!
Huh?! Uh-oh!
♪ Da da da-da da da ♪
Finn! Kill it!
I can't find its
magic-gem weak spot.
FINN:
Oh! There it is.
Ya-a-a-a-a-h!
[WARBLE!]
[LAUGHS]
I did it! I helped!
I'm the sexiest adventurer
in the world.
Tree Trunks, you're not
an adventurer!
You nearly got yourself
killed -- again!
Do you want to die,
Tree Trunks?!
Is that what you think
adventurers do --
die and make all their friends
feel terrible
'cause they
couldn't save you?!
[SNIFFLES]
Whoa, man.
L-I'm going home now.
[SOBBING]
[SIGHS]
Tree Trunks...
Tree Trunks!
Don't follow me!
Oh, Finn,
you shouldn't yell at cuties
that just
want to help you.
Ohh!
Man, I feel horrible.
I was only yelling because
I care about her safety.
That's what happens
when you care too much, dude.
[TREE TRUNKS SCREAMS
IN DISTANCE]
BOTH: [PANTING] Tree Trunks!
Finn!
I found the crystal gem apple.
[TWINKLE!]
Whoo-hoo!
You're the man, Tree Trunks.
Tree Trunks, I'm a huge butt guy
for getting mad at you.
I'm a huge fart.
I was only upset
because I love you and I don't
wanna see you get hurt.
That's precious, Finn.
And I'll accept
your apology
if you let me
kiss your cheek.
Uh...
I don't -- I don't know. I --
Whoa.
Let her kiss your cheek, man.
It's a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity.
[DISTORTED]
Whoa!
BOTH:
Huh?
Let her kiss your cheek, man.
It's a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity.
Uh... I don't know.
A crystal guardian!
Tree Trunks, stay out
of the monster battle this time.
I don't want you getting hurt.
All right.
I promise I will.
Radical!
Back off, you!
Stop copying me!
[GROWLS]
Aaaaaah!
[CLUNK!]
Aaaah!
[GRUNTS]
Ow!
Finn!
[GROWLS]
[CLUNK!]
Ohh!
Ow!
He's copying
everything we do.
[HUMMING]
[TUNE PLAYING]
Hey,
it's my butterfly friend.
That's precious.
♪ Da da-da da da da da ♪
Whoo!
Shake it, Tree Trunks!
♪ Da da-da da da da ♪
Jam clam!
Let's beat it up
while it's copying Tree Trunks.
BOTH:
Ya-a-a-a-h!
Oh, crud.
This is barf, dude.
Oh, man!
I'm a total moron.
We got to fight this one
Tree Trunks-style.
I'll get the makeup!
[MID-TEMPO VIOLIN MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, crystal guardian!
Are you okay with Tree Trunks
taking a bite of that apple?
- I'm okay with it.
- And I'm stupid.
[LAUGHS]
You heard the guardian, T.T.
Bite that thing.
Okay!
[MUNCH!]
Whoo!
How's it taste, Tree Trunks?
Yeah, how is it?
[POP!]
[LOW-PITCHED THROAT SINGING]
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪