[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on,
grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to
very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
[SWISH!]
Whoop! Huh?
Oop! Whoopee.
Cheers,
Lumpy Space Princess.
[ALL CHEERING, LAUGHING]
JAKE:
Yeah! Bouncing!
Princess, this tea party
sucks in a big way,
but thanks for the invite.
Oh, don't worry, Finn.
The mallow tea ceremony takes
years to master.
Princess, I think
I just now mastered it.
[SPLASH!]
One more bounce.
All right.
[GRUNTS]
Tea-partying's hard,
huh, Jake?
Oof! Yes.
What? No way.
It's super-easy.
Lumpy Space Princess,
you big faker.
You're floating, not bouncing.
Fine. I'll prove it.
Huh? Aah!
Oh, no! Oh, snap!
[CRUNCH!]
Aah!
Ah, lame.
Sorry I bit your leg.
You're still biting me!
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, right. Sorry.
Dude, your leg!
JAKE:
This is... new.
Nothing ominous, though --
just a bump.
Nah -- that's no bump.
It's the early stage
of the lumps.
Is it serious?
It just means he's changing
into a Lumpy Space guy,
on account of my bite.
It's just like, um, you know,
werewolf rules.
Arrr! Arr-arr-arr! Arr!
- Oh, no!
- What?
You think I'm gonna turn
all lumpy, like her?
Get outta here!
Wha?!
Finn, I think
I'm freaking out!
Calm down, bud.
I'll... I'll sock the
lumpiness out of you.
PRINCESS:
Hey, now.
[GRUNTING]
Royal intervention.
Surely there must be
an antidote to the lumps.
Yeah, there's an antidote,
but you have to go
all the way
to Lumpy Space to get it,
and Jake has to use it
by sunset.
What happens if he doesn't take
the antidote by sunset?
He'll be lumpy,
like, forever.
LSP, please, can you tell us
how to reach Lumpy Space?
Yeah, I mean, there's
a portal nearby.
I can show you whenever.
BOTH:
Take us now! Take us now!
[STOMACH GROWLS]
I should not have
drank that much tea.
Don't go telling everyone
about this portal or whatever.
It's kind of a secret.
Where is it?
The portal is that
frog and mushroom.
Ribbit!
Password, please.
Whatevers 2009!
Good day, Princess.
Is your father okay with you
entering Lumpy Space
with two...
[CREAK!]
...non-lumpers?
Just say "yes!"
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yeah, whatever. Fine.
[SLURP! WHIP! WHIP! WHIP!]
Aaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Aah!
Whoa! Lumpy Space!
So, where's the antidote?
- Hold it.
First, you should
check out my house.
It's, like, kind of lame,
but way less lame than,
like, your house.
Uh, can you skip to the part
where you'll tell us
where the antidote is?
It's up there at
make-out point.
That's so close!
We can run there in no...
time.
Aw, what?!
It's like a million-mile
fall into space!
Yeah, you have to travel
by car in my world,
or else you'll fall into
the Lumpy Abyss.
LUMPY SPACE KING:
Daughter!
Have you brought smooth people
into our domain?!
I had to, Dad.
I'm trying to help them.
So don't lumping yell at me!
What did you say?!
What did you just say?!
I said, "lump off, mom!"
[SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[HUFFING]
- Uhh...
- What?!
- Vroom... vroom?
- Oh, yeah, I need to borrow the car.
You have made
your mother cry
for the last time, daughter!
You are hereby banned
from using the royal car!
Shucks!
I lumping hate them!
I'm really,
really sorry, Finn,
but I can't help you,
because my parents
are horrible idiots!
Don't you know anyone
else with a car?
My friend Melissa has a car,
but she's dating
my ex-boyfriend Brad.
Call her...
now!
Hmm.
Call "BBF 66."
[CELLPHONE RINGS]
Hello?
Hey, Melissa. What's up?
- What's she saying?
- I'm asking her! Geez!
Melissa, just listen.
MELISSA:
Have you forgotten what day this is?
Melissa, I'm trying to
help out some friends.
Tonight is the weekly
Promcoming dance!
- Oh, glob. I forgot.
- What'd she say?
Tonight is the weekly
Promcoming dance!
It's gonna be so flippin'
awesome!
LSP, we don't have
time for this.
Ask for the ride, LSP.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh.
Wha?!
[AS LSP] Melissa, you
should totally drive us
to make-out point...
to make out with hot boys.
LSP, you're so ba-a-a-a-a-d!
Be there in a sec!
- Bye-ah!
[CELLPHONE BEEPS]
Hmph.
[NORMAL VOICE] Sorry, but
Jake's lumpiness is worsening.
Actually, I think I'm beating it back
with sheer willpower.
[POP!]
Oh, my.
Yeah, whatever.
Just don't mess with
my phone again.
Hey!
Ugh. Okay.
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
[UP-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS]
Aw, Finn, this music
"ducks, " right?
[LUMPY VOICE]
Aw, I love this song.
We should totally T. P.
Shawndala's house.
[NORMAL VOICE]
Gracious!
That was terrible!
Finn, if you can't save me
from the lumps,
if I do turn,
if I become lumpy
like them,
I want you to --
- it's not gonna come to that!
But if it does,
I'll bury you
beneath the nicest,
most shadiest tree.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
I'm saying that
if I go totally lumpy,
then I want you to get
used to lumpy Jake.
What did you thlnk
I was saylng?
Oh, um...
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
Can't this car go any faster?!
MELISSA:
We're already here.
Hi, Finn.
We've been here for, like,
five minutes.
Finally! Huh?
This doesn't look like
make-out point.
This is Brad's house.
You wanted a ride to
make-out point?
You think I want to
make out with you?!
Uhh...
Well, maybe I do, but...
wait!
I have a boyfriend, Finn!
[WHOOSH! CLANK!]
LSP, we got to hurry!
Jake's running out of time!
Hey, this is hard for me, too.
I mean, I used to eat
chili-cheese fries with Brad,
so there's gonna be a lot of
romantic tension on this ride.
BRAD:
Hey.
Oh, Brad.
[GIGGLES]
You miss me yet, LSP?
Scooch over, Finn.
I'm gonna sit in the back.
This is it.
Let's go.
Wait.
Watch yourself, Finn.
The guys who
use the antidote up here
are notorious for being...
smooth posers.
What does that mean?
It just means what it means.
Hurry.
Get the antidote
so we can get out of here.
Thanks, LSP.
Bu-u-u-u-mps.
Um... bumps.
Uh, yeah... bumps.
Aw, man!
[PANTING]
Hey, guys.
- Lookin' smooth.
- Really?
You think we're smooth?
Well, mostly you in the center,
but yeah.
Why are you sucking up to us?
My best friend needs
an antidote for lumpiness.
Yeah, lumpiness sucks.
Hey, Monty, time's up,
sphere hog.
My turn.
[ZAP!]
So, the antidote is in
that orb you were sitting on.
This orb ls the antidote, brah.
Can my friend borrow it?
Yeah, sure, as long as you
give it right back.
Ham-a-cow!
Thanks, fellas.
What's taking so long?
Did those smooth-heads give you
the orb already or what?
Wait!
Is this another
"friend" of yours?
What do you care?
Just give him the antidote already
and stop
being such a poser.
Sorry, kid.
We changed our minds.
Why did you have to say
all those rude things to them?!
What? I was helping you.
Thanks a lot!
They were right about to hand
over the antidote!
You're welcome a lot.
You insulted them,
and they got mad,
and now Jake's gonna be
lumpy forever!
This is all your fault!
Wow. Now I know how
you really feel.
I was just trying to help,
but whatever.
[SNIFFLES]
No. No, not "whatever."
[VOICE BREAKING] I know I
mess things up sometimes,
but I'm really trying,
and you're supposed
to be my friend --
not like the fake ones
I have here.
So do what you want!
I'm going to Promcoming!
Are you coming or not,
Lumpy Jake?
No.
Because no matter
how messed-up and lumpy I get,
this guy never turns
his back on me.
[LUMPY VOICE] Oh, yeah.
Right behind you.
Just got to turn my
back on this guy.
Jake!
It's almost sunset!
Jake --
didn't save him.
L...
[GROWLING, SNARLING]
I'll kill you,
Lumpy Spa-a-a-ce!
- MONTY: Jam on, man.
- Huh?
I thought you guys left.
We were drawn back by your
Plaintive Wail.
We dig your directionless fury.
Um, thanks.
Respect.
Here.
Pyoo! Take it.
Win your girl back.
Yeah, there's no girl.
But there ls still
time to save Jake.
Do you guys know where
Promcoming is?
Promcoming takes place way
down on that land lump.
FINN:
Awesome.
Do any of y'all have wheels?
Nah, we were all ditched here,
just like you.
Well, you think I could
make it to that land lump
if I jumped off this cliff?
- You kidding?
A smoothie like you
will plummet
right into the eternal void!
What if I was lumpy?
Could I float over?
No, no!
It's too dangerous!
I'd say there's a 50/50 chance
of you making it.
That's good enough for me.
Now bite me!
- Are you crazy, man?!
- What are you talking about?!
Raaaaaaah!
Aaah! Aaah! Ooooh--
Yes!
I can feel the multiple bites
accelerating the
lumpification process!
I'm starting to float!
Don't jump, guy!
I have to -- for my buddy.
Raaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Wow. He's insane.
[CRASH!]
I made it!
And there he is!
Yeah, Promcoming.
Yeah, cool.
Jake, I'm mostly lumpy now,
and I totally think you
should sit on this sphere.
- No! Hey!
- Sit on it!
[GRUNTING]
No!
Please, Jake!
You're my best friend!
Just sit on the sphere!
Pshaw!
I remember you.
You're just a smoothie-
wannabe-lumpy poser.
Sit on it!
Before I turn completely lumpy!
- No!
- Oh, no!
I can feel the lumpiness
about to consume me!
[LUMPY VOICE]
Oh, yeah.
Being lumpy is the best.
Hey, stop talking to yourself,
dumb guy.
Take your ball
and get out of here.
Fine! I don't want you
to have it anyways!
So I can't have it now, eh?
That's right!
It's mine!
Gimme that ball!
No! You can't have it!
Give it to me!
- No!
I want it!
Give it to me!
You want it that bad?
Go get it, then!
Bumps! Byahhh--
[BABBLING]
[GASPS]
[NORMAL VOICE] Oh, I'm
not lumpy anymore!
Oh, no!
Finn, buddy!
You got to sit on this!
- No!
You can't make me, smoothi--
oof!
JAKE:
[ECHOING] Finn?
Hey, Finn. Hey, buddy.
- Finn!
- Huh?
[NORMAL VOICE]
Hey, dude. We made it.
Man, there's something
cold under my butt.
Oh!
[LAUGHS]
The antidote.
Just in time, too.
LSP, I'm sorry I blew up
at you before.
I didn't mean it.
I was just really stressed out.
You know, it's fine.
You and Jake can
make it up to me
by dancing this
last dance with me.
Sounds good to me.
What do you say, Jake?
[LUMPY VOICE]
That sounds totally lame.
- [BOTH GASP]
- [LAUGHS]
[NORMAL VOICE] I'm just kidding.
Let's dance!
[UP-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS]
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪