[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on, grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to very
distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog
and Finn the human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
[VIOLIN PLAYING SLOWLY]
Are you okay, dude?
Yeah. Why?
You look bored.
Nah.
That's just how I look when
I'm listening to music.
Well, good, because I'm
about to kick it up a notch.
Bring it.
[VIOLIN PLAYING SLOWLY]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Who do you think it is?
Could be anybody.
I can't quite make it out.
[GASPS]
Aah! it's the lce King!
The lce King?!
I think this is
the right address.
Maybe this is --
is this West?
Hyah!
Yeah, kick his butt, dude!
Wah! Wah! Wah!
Eat my sword, lce King!
Yeah! Aw!
You cannot defeat me, child!
I will, though,
with a sweet kick!
Psych!
[GRUNTS]
Aah!
Unh!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Now I can kill you!
Oh, wait. Wait, wait.
Oh, I am so stupid!
Silly Billy!
I came by to tell
you the good news.
What's the good news?
I'm getting married to someone
who wants to marry me.
[GASPS]
My betrothed is
right over there.
Hi, honey.
Hey, cool guy.
I'm a lucky guy.
I didn't even have
to kidnap this one.
She fell in love with me the moment I
slipped on her engagement ring.
Ew!
Bye-bye!
[LAUGHS]
The lady penguins are throwing her
one of those "Bachelorette" parties.
This is weird, dude.
Hmm.
If you get married,
what about capturing Princesses?
Oh, well.
No more capturing pretty
Princesses for this lce King.
[LAUGHS]
Oh.
Well, fare thee well, lce King.
Huh?
Yeah, good luck with thee
and thy creepy wedding.
We totally support your decision
to stop capturing Princesses.
I'm happy for him.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
Sure wish someone would throw
me a bachelorette party --
Oh, I mean,
"Manlerette" party.
But we hate you.
If you won't throw
me a Manlerette party,
then I'll never have my last hurrah before
buckling down with that battle axe!
It'll drive me back to a life
of stealing hot Princesses!
Is that what you want?!
No. No, no, no, no, no.
Dude, we got to show him a
good time and treat him right.
Otherwise, he'll go back
to imprisoning ladies.
L-I can't have that! I --
Shh! I know.
I know that you can't have that.
Don't worry.
All right,
let's go party, lce King.
[GIGGLES]
[TECHNO MUSIC PLAYING]
Best Manlerette party ever!
[LAUGHING]
Bah! Aah!
[LAUGHS]
Now I'm gonna go get marrled!
[GIGGLES]
[SINGSONG VOICE]
I'm gonna get married!
Bye, lce King! Good luck!
Have fun being married!
No more stealing Princesses!
Yeah -- wait.
No more st-stealing Princesses?
Wow.
BOTH:
What?!
L-I didn't realize I'd have to
give up stealing the ladies.
But you said you
were fine with it.
I know what I said,
but, you know,
sometimes you say
things and then you
don't really mean them.
Wha-- are you serious?
I'm just not sure I want to
get married in such a hurry.
What if she's just after my demonic
wishing eye and ghost pouch?
[LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
We just took you out partying
so that you could feel
better about getting hitched!
Maybe I'll just go back
to capturing lots of girls.
It's what I feel
comfortable doing, you know?
Being free, wind at my back,
lots of girls, kidnapping 'em.
All right, here comes
my double kick!
Finn, Finn,
cool yourself, buddy.
We need to get this guy married,
remember?
Yeah, I remember.
Watch.
Let big brother handle this.
Hey, lce King,
don't be nervous.
Marriage is the most beautiful thing
that could ever happen to a jerk like you.
Oh, really? Why?
Why?
Poots, that guy is good.
Why? Why?!
Jake.
Not now!
Why? Why?
Why? Why? Why?
My mind is made up 80% sure --
No marriage.
Well, uh, don't you, uh, want to
grow old with somebody, right?
Just like these old swans.
[SMOOCHING]
Bleh, those stinky,
old swans.
Huh?
[SLURPS]
[GULPS]
[LAUGHS]
ALL:
What?!
Oh, now I get what you
guys are trying to tell me.
Marriage is a thing that allows
me to capture a Princess forever
and let her live inside of me.
[CRYING]
Marriage is the most
beautiful thing in the world!
Uh...
yeah, I-l never, uh...
I guess it is.
Jake, this is bad news, man.
We got to go tell him that
he can't eat his wife.
Eh, let's cross that
bridge when we get to it.
Look at how happy he is.
The wedding -- back on 100%!
[LAUGHS]
Whew!
All that's left is
the lousy wedding.
I'm weddy for the wedding!
[BELLS TOLLING]
[RHYTHMIC CLATTERING]
You know, even though
the lce King is a wad,
I'm pretty happy for him.
JAKE:
Uh-huh.
This wedding looks lame, man.
Be prepared to be bored
out of your mind.
[CHUCKLES]
LCE KING:
Finn, Jake, you made it.
Come on up here.
I'm almost finished
tying up my bride.
Weird.
And your bride is lnto that?
This is a traditional wedding ritual
for good luck in the lce Kingdom.
You see, she'll be hoisted up
and then lowered down.
And when she touches my beard
from above, she will be my Queen.
[GIGGLING]
Well, cool, man.
I'm glad y'all are happy...
being crazy together.
Thank you.
Excuse me as we finish
preparing for the nuptials.
2, 4, 8, 16, 20, uh...
32.
Yes, 32, 64, 100
And...
Huh?!
Her eyes are huge.
I'm gonna go check 'em out.
Stop scratching your ear, man.
It's gross.
It wasn't me.
It was my foot, dude.
Whoa, you've got ridiculously
large eyes, Princess.
Are you allergic to something?
No, Finn.
I was just born like this.
Why are you crying?
I'm not crying, Finn.
My tear sack is broken.
Help me!
What?!
I didn't say anything.
The lce King cursed me!
You've got to set me free!
I would rather die than
marry the lce King!
[BOTH GASP]
He tricked me!
And I was happy for
that son of a toot!
Look at her ring.
She fell in love with me the moment
I slipped on her engagement ring.
FINN:
That's what cursed her!
Don't worry, Princess.
I'll remove this ring
and save your life.
No, she's my love boat!
No, man, you cursed her!
She hates you!
Okay, that's your opinion!
Wait a minute.
[SIGHS]
So, you knew she
was cursed all along,
which means you knew
she wasn't trying to steal your
demonic eye junk or whatever,
and you knew you
had total control of her.
Yeah, yes, that's right.
So then why did you make
us go through all that junk
about why marriage
is worth stuff?!
Oh, I don't know.
I'm complicated --
and spontaneous.
[CHUCKLES]
That's probably why
she wants to marry me.
She wants to marry you because
you brainwashed her!
Silence!
BOTH:
Whoa, wait!
Aw, man!
It's time for the
lowering ceremony!
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
Hoist her up!
[GRUNTING]
[ROPE CREAKING]
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
Commence the lowering!
[ROPE CREAKING]
[GASPS]
Hyah!
Yes, nothing can
stop me now.
Hyah!
Oh! Whoa! Unh!
Bl-bl-bl-bl-bl!
What is wrong with you, man?!
Aah!
[GRUNTING]
Strangling the groom's
nose at a wedding?!
Aaaah!
What's wrong with you?!
You're the one that there's
something wrong with!
Aaaaaaah!
Huh?!
[GRUNTS]
Gotcha!
Thanks, man.
[CHUCKLES]
No problem.
[GROANS]
I think you
dropped something.
Catch!
- Huh?
[GRUNTS]
Whoa!
Jake!
[MOANS]
[GRUNTS]
What? What?
Jake!
[GRUNTING]
Oh, hey.
- Hey.
You got the ring
off her finger?
JAKE:
Huh? Oh, oh, yeah.
Now she's not hypnotized.
But we're still frozen.
I got a plan.
Oh, good.
Now let's try that again.
Lower her!
You lousy, butt-faced pig!
I hate you!
Here she comes.
Yes, touch my beard, deary.
Yes, that's right.
Almost there.
Now!
[GRUNTS]
Oh!
I'm married, right,
Snowman?
Yes, it's official.
It's official!
You done married a dog, dude!
What?
What's that supposed to --
Oh, no.
[LAUGHING]
Wait, what the --
What am I laughing about?
[SIGHS]
And now everything's
back to normal.
Well, I wouldn't
say everything.
Come on, guys.
Help me celebrate
my un-marriage.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪