[MOUSE SQUEAKS]
[PENGUINS CHIRP]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SCREECHES]
♪ Adventure Time ♪
♪ Come on,
grab your friends ♪
♪ We'll go to
very distant lands ♪
♪ With Jake the dog ♪
♪ And Finn the Human ♪
♪ The fun will never end ♪
♪ It's Adventure Time ♪
Hey, Jake?
Yeah?
You ever wonder what a
demon's heart looks like?
Of course, dude.
You ever wonder what a
demon's heart tastes like?
EVIL VOICE:
Hey, kid, you want some magic powers?
Magic powers
for absolutely free.
Heck yeah!
Wait!
Let's not be too rash.
Just look at this guy.
Check out the sunken,
lifeless eyes,
the foul stench of decay.
You know what that means?
It means he's evil, I guess.
Well, evil, sure, but
mostly, he's unattractive, and
unattractive people are desperate.
You should haggle with him.
Hey, I want more than
just free powers.
What else you got?
All right.
Free magical powers and...
[CRACKING]
...and this keychain.
Oh, oh, oh!
Play it cool, Finn.
Right.
I begrudgingly accept your offer.
Yes!
Then the deal is struck.
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
You can pick up your powers
right through that door.
This way.
[WIND HOWLING]
[PBHT!]
[GRUNTS]
This place looks magical.
You think this is where we
get the powers?
Yes, I do.
Free powers for all.
Want some?
Yeah!
Are you the guy
handing them out?
You seek Bufo the Wizard.
So, where is that guy?
He is here, of course.
Uh...
He's here?
But he's not you?
That's right.
We should beat him up
until he starts making sense.
[GROANS]
ALL:
We are Bufo.
Oh!
ALL:
So... So...
...you wish to be
inducted into the ancient --
...ancient order --
Dang it, Leonard.
If we don't talk at the same
time, nobody can understand us.
Sorry. Geez.
ALL:
Ahem!
So, you want free wizard powers,
powers like... these!
[LAUGHS]
Yeah!
BOTH:
We want them.
Give us the stuff.
- Yes, we do.
- Can't wait.
ALL:
Then follow me.
BOTH:
Whoo-hoo!
ALL:
Behold the grand hall of
wizardry.
This is where young potentials
train to become ultimate wizards.
But most are not ready for the
responsibility that comes with it.
I'm responsible, dude.
So am I.
That's a lie.
It is a lie.
And I take full
responsibility for it.
ALL:
Yes, yes, very
responsible.
Now I bestow upon you these...
wizard cloaks!
BOTH:
Whoa!
Hey, this is a dress.
Yeah. And I am into it.
It's like gossamer.
[GRUNTING]
This way, I won't be embarrassed.
ALL:
Fine, fine.
Now, for every power that you
accrue, you shall receive a star
badge like these.
This final star betokens the
rank of ultimate wizard.
BOTH:
Whoa!
Mark me, Jake.
I shall have that final star.
Where do we start?
ALL:
Level 1 -- Dustomancy.
Yeah!
Dustomancy, whatever that is.
Gimme, gimme, gimme,
gimme, gimme!
ALL:
To receive this power,
you must first...
eat these brooms.
[ZIP! ZIP!]
All right.
[GAGS]
Wait.
[SPITS]
This is gross.
Man, I can't eat this.
Yeah, you can.
Do what I do.
[GROWLS]
Ahh!
[GULPS]
[SQUEAK!]
Oops.
Ah, there we go.
[BOTH GASP]
Whoa, you got a star.
[CHUCKLES]
Observe my magics.
Wait, Jake.
Don't use them until
I finish my broom.
[GROWLING]
[GULPS]
Last... bite.
Dude, you got your
star, too.
We're Dustomancers!
[GRUNTS]
Nothing happened.
This is a total rip-off.
Bufo, you tricked us.
Stupid power doesn't even work.
ALL:
Calm yourself, boy.
You are acting hysterical.
Do you not see that you are
using Dustomancy?
Behold.
I'm doing this?
So... l have --
ALL:
Yes!
Mastery over all dust motes.
You can also read their
emotions.
For instance, this mote is very
unhappy in his marriage.
That's... sort of cool.
Sort of cool?
This is radical!
Whoo, yeah!
Force that enthusiasm.
ALL:
Are you ready for more magic?
We get more?
ALL:
So much more.
Like level 2 -- the power of
shadowcery.
You can't see through those,
right?
Nope, not at all.
ALL:
To gain provenance over
the shadows, place your hands
into this bowl.
What bowl?
ALL:
No! Cover your eyes!
[GROANS]
Fine.
ALL:
Thrust your hands into
this bowl... of eyeballs.
Eyeballs?!
Dude, it's okay.
They're just peeled grapes.
ALL:
No!
They're eyeballs.
[GIGGLE]
Yuck!
ALL:
Well done.
You have groped the eyeballs
fearlessly.
Another star! Yeah!
Shadowcery.
[HORSE NEIGHS, GRUNTS]
Onward, my shadow steed.
Huh?
No touchies.
Wizard powers
are so cool.
I want all the star badges!
ALL:
Excellent.
[LAUGHS]
[CLING! CLING! CLING!]
ALL:
Well done.
[LAUGHS]
[BOTH GULPING]
[WHOOSH!]
[MUMBLES]
[WHOOSH! WHOOSH!]
[SHING!]
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Whoa!
All we're missing
now is the big star.
You ready to complete
the set, man?
Nah, I'm good.
What?!
How can you stop now?
Eh, I got everything I
need -- a limitless supply of
mayonnaise, this captivating new
hairstyle, and I just learned
the best spell of all.
What's that?
Sleep.
[SNORING]
Aw, what a lame-o.
Bufo, I'm ready to
get that big star.
ALL:
To tell true, the last
power is not free.
Wha?
You can't do this to me, man.
I've got no money.
ALL:
No. No cash.
For the final star, you must
take... the pledge of ultimate
responsibility.
Okay, I'll take that
pledge.
ALL:
Are you sure?
Perhaps you are not
sufficiently familiar with --
I'm ready.
ALL:
Well, there may be
ramifications that you cannot --
just let me take that
pledge, man!
ALL:
My word, I've never met
someone so irresponsibly
responsible.
Very well, then.
You must... grasp... my hand.
That's it? Easy.
Whoa!
[GROANS]
Huh?
[GASPS]
My big star!
Yes! Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
Wait. Where am I?
ALL:
Direct your attention to
the scale-model orb.
Huh?
Is that an
asteroid heading for
this very temple?
ALL:
Yes.
It's been heading for this
temple for 847 years.
Only the magic of the ultimate
wizards keeps it from getting
any closer.
Quickly, add your power to that
of the orb.
Oh, okay.
Whoa!
I got it. Now what?
ALL:
Now I release the elder
Jeremy from his pledge.
Razzamafoo!
It's about time.
ALL:
And you take his place
for the rest of
your natural life.
Awesome.
Wait. What?
ALL:
This is what you signed
up for when you took the...
pledge of ultimate
responsibility.
This is what all the
wizard training was about?
You tricked me!
Young wizard!
The asteroid approaches.
Oh, yeah, sorry.
[WARBLE! WARBLE!]
ALL:
I tricked you, of
course, but would anyone ever
volunteer to do this?
I'm out.
Aw, man, this sucks.
[GROANS]
Old people, there's
got to be a better way.
Nope.
This is how the ancient ones
wanted it.
Yeah?
I got a younger idea.
[GRUNTS]
You fool!
Your newfangled thinking will
get us all killed!
Youth culture forever!
Whoa!
ALL:
Hey, have you gone crazy?
Get back in
the bouncy harness.
Sleep.
ALL:
You are -- [MOANS]
[SNORING]
Ultimate wizardry,
activate!
Uh... hmm.
Maybe my footing's off?
There you go.
I cast dragon eyes...
tiger claw...
vorpal hand...
blazing feet...
beauteous wings...
and finally,
every other power I
didn't mention by name!
With all my
magics combined, I'm
powerful enough to move the
entire village out of the
asteroid's path.
[STRAINING]
[SNORING]
[STRAINING CONTINUES]
[GASPS]
I need some help.
Jake, awaken!
Reflect.
Hey, I'm alive.
What's that up there?
[GASPS]
Oh, no!
Aw, my stupid young
idea will be responsible for
hundreds of deaths.
It sure will.
Huh?
Old wizards, you ditched your
responsibilities to help me.
What?! No!
We left so we wouldn't be killed
by that asteroid.
Oh, okay.
Um, since you're here already,
can you lend me a hand?
[ALL STRAINING]
[ZIP! WHOOSH!]
[SNORES]
[WHOOSH!]
Huh?
Whoo-hoo!
Nice job.
Thanks to us,
the village is saved,
and we reclaimed a few of
your twilight years.
ALL:
Don't forget to thank me,
for this was my plan for
all of these 847 years.
No way.
Your plan
was to dupe a
succession of
rubes into keeping
the asteroid at bay.
ALL:
Perhaps you're right.
No more giving out free powers.
I hereby renounce all magic.
[SNIFFLES, CRIES]
My life is over!!
Chill, man.
You don't have
to quit your job.
ALL:
I don't?
Nah, just don't take
credit for ideas that aren't
yours.
ALL:
Oh. Okay. Good idea.
Glad I thought of it.
EVIL VOICE:
Hey, naked kid, you want some
free... demon heart?
Full circle!
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ And the butterflies and bees ♪
♪ We can wander through the forest ♪
♪ And do so as we please ♪
♪ Come along with me ♪
♪ To a cliff under a tree ♪